bu
bu
[Music]
[Música]
he
he
e
e
[Music]
[Música]
he
he
k he
k he
[Applause] [Music]
[Aplausos]
T ah
T ah
[Music] [
[Música]
Applause] [
[Aplausos]
Good afternoon family well I don't promise
Buenas tardes familia bueno no prometo
anything eh I don't promise anything I'm here I'm
nada eh No prometo nada estoy aquí estoy
here trying more or less to get back on track but
aquí intentando más o menos retomar pero
[Music]
[Música]
eh As usual as
eh Como ya es costumbre como ya es
usual every month a month and a half
costumbre cada mes mes y medio
approximately every month a month and a half
aproximadamente cada mes mes y medio
approximately
aproximadamente
eh I'm really bad I'm really bad with my
eh estoy malillo estoy malillo con la
throat I'm really bad with my throat
garganta estoy malillo con la garganta
man and the truth is that my
una barbaridad tío y la verdad es que
voice well my voice It's not that I
tengo la voz bueno la voz No es que la
have a bad voice I always have a bad voice but
tenga fea siempre la tengo fea pero sí
I'm really touched man yes I am
que estoy muy tocado tío sí que estoy
really touched and it's that I  it hurts it hurts
muy tocado y es que me duele me duele
so I'm going to be here for a bit I'm
entonces voy a estar un poquito por aquí
going to deal with the issues that I had
voy a tratar los temas que tenía por
pending here I don't know if I'll have time
aquí pendiente No sé si me va dar tiempo
to deal with them all I'll let you know because if I
a tratarlos todos Ya os aviso porque si
see that the live show is very unbearable
veo que el directo es muy insoportable
with the cough and all that I'll close and
con la tos y demás cierro y ya lo
we'll resume tomorrow the day after but I warn you I warn you who warns is
retomaremos mañana pasado pero aviso
not a traitor okay I
aviso el que avisa no es traidor vale he
recorded a video for the main channel
grabado vídeo para el canal principal
but of course recording is not the same because you
pero claro grabar no es lo mismo porque
're editing okay and check your
estás editando vale y chequéate las
defenses rebit It's that I think that already
defensas rebit Es que yo creo que ya
well the defenses let's see I have
bueno las defensas a ver yo tengo
chom disease the defenses are always
enfermedad de chom las defensas siempre
touched but it's been a lot of days
tocadas pero ya llevo un montón de días
Eh When was the live show with Fran on
Eh Cuándo fue el directo con Fran el
Wednesday No well since Wednesday
miércoles No pues desde el miércoles el
Wednesday on the way back I was already with the
miércoles a la vuelta ya venía con la
well during the live show with Fran I was already
bueno durante el directo con Fran ya
coughing a lot
tosía mucho
and on the way back on the way back I remember
y ya a la vuelta a la vuelta me acuerdo
along the way that I recorded that video with
por el camino que grabé el vídeo ese de
Juan Guarnizo and there he was touched touched
Juan guarnizo y ahí venía tocado tocado
eh No Elena it calms it down it calms it down
eh No Elena me lo calma me lo calma
both the cold and the heat what
tanto el frío como el calor lo que me
hurts me It's when I cough when I cough it does this to
duele Es al tocer al tocer me hace así
me  it hits me when I cough it hits me like a
me pega al tocer es que me pega p un
bump on the roof of my mouth
zasta en el cielo de la boca
dude it relieves me it relieves the cold and the
tía me alivia me alivia el frío y el
heat too it relieves me the cold and
calor también me alivia el frío y me
the heat relieves me the truth is it
alivia el calor la verdad
relieves the cold and the heat relieves me
me alivia el frío y me alivia el calor
both on one hand the heat sort of
las dos cosas por un lado el calor como
softens it and on the other hand the
que me lo suaviza y por otro lado el
cold too I don't understand I don't know why
frío también no entiendo no sé por qué
but yes yes it tastes good to me both the cold
pero sí sí me me sabe bien tanto el frío
and the heat I mean but no not things that aren't
o el calor o sea pero no no cosas que no
natural not natural I don't want
estén al natural no al natural no quiero
anything
nada
but but dude it's not about my
pero pero tía no se trata de las
defenses it's about the fact that I'm going to have to have
defensas se trata de que me voy a tener
surgery do you remember that we were
que operar os acordáis que estuvimos
talking the other day with the joke about having
hablando el otro día con el cachondeo de
cosmetic surgery do you remember that we talked about having
estética os acordáis que lo hablamos lo
surgery noos this for cosmetic reasons to get
de operar noos esto por estética para
rid of a little bit of my
que me quitara un poquito de
double chin so we're going to do it we're going to do it let's
papada pues le vamos a hacer lo vamos a
see the whole thing about having surgery
hacer a ver es que el rollo de operarme
on that let's see I saw it Well I
de eso a ver se lo vi Bueno a auron se
heard Auron just recently no he says
lo escuchaba ahora hace poco no que dice
that he has to be
que tiene que estar casi todo el mes de
out of work for most of May for that and I think it was
mayo de baja por eso y a creo que fue
Play I think the  nter Play once
Play creo que el nter Play una vez
spent like a long time using
estuvo como un montón de tiempo usando
Artificial Intelligence for that reason for an
Inteligencia artificial por eso por una
operation and I think it was like
operación y yo creo que fue de
that recently I think he said that it was like
eso hace poco me suena que dijo que era
that now whether it's true or not I don't
de eso ahora que fuera verdad o no No lo
know but it seems to me that it seems to me that he said that
sé pero me suena que me suena que dijo
eh is it true or have I smoked a
eso eh es verdad o me he fumado yo un
joint but the nauter Play wasn't there for
porro pero el nauter Play no estuvo
that long not with with one let's see one
tanto tiempo no con con una a ver a una
is bad we could record with AI eh we
es mala podríamos grabar con ia eh
could record newscasts with an
podríamos grabar noticieros con una
AI I'll manage I'll manage
ia ya me las apañar Yo ya me las apañar
but I think that I think it's
yo pero yo creo que yo creo que es
indisputable it was for that very reason Yes true I have
indiscutible fue por eso mismo Sí verdad
n't dreamed about it but I'll manage
no lo he soñado pero ya me las apañar yo
eh I'll manage and I would do things I'm not
eh Ya me las apañar yo y haría cosas no
going to be unemployed for three weeks or two weeks I
voy a estar tres semanas ni dos semanas
'm not even one
parado no estoy ni una ya me las apañar
I'll manage with the Editors and we would see what we would
yo con los Editores y veríamos qué
do
haríamos
but but yes it's true that I have to have an
pero pero sí que es verdad que que yo
operation
eso me lo tengo que operar
100% tomorrow tomorrow I'll meet you tomorrow yes
100% mañana mañana os reuní mañana sí
there I've been preparing it I already have
ahí lo he estado preparando ya lo tengo
half prepared tomorrow's thing between
medio preparado lo de mañana entre
gossip between gossip but for  here is that I've
salseo entre salseo pero por aquí es que
been here that all week I haven't
llevo por aquí que en toda la semana no
done almost anything, I mean the only thing I
he hecho casi nada o sea lo único que
did was that video that ju
hice fue el vídeo ese de ju
made
hizo
Oh and I did nothing else and I did nothing
Ay y no hice más nada y no hice más
else gargling with aguardiente to burn
nada gárgaras de aguardiente para quemar
the tonsils grandmother's remedy But what
las anginas remedio de abuela Pero qué
aguardiente What is
aguardiente Qué es
aguardiente it's not for cleaning
aguardiente no es para para limpiar
aguardiente it's not something to clean the
aguardiente no es algo para limpiar los
rooms bathrooms you're ripping me off eh Hey do
cuartos baños me estáis timando eh Oye
n't start giving me
no me empecéis a dar consejos de los
your advice eh because I think that what I have to
vuestros eh que yo creo que lo que tengo
do is have surgery and To get rid of those
que hacer y a operarme y A quitarme la
junk out
las cacharra esas fuera
eh a
eh un
liquor gargling with water and salt is silly let's
licor gargaras de agua y sal es tontería
see what I have to do today is
a ver lo que tengo que hacer hoy es
rest after the live
descansar después del directo
and tomorrow let's see if I'll go I mean in the
y y mañana a ver si ya me voy o sea al
end it's time
final es tiempo
eh Javi the strong water is from
eh Javi el agua fuerte es el del cuarto
Javi's room you never waited at danina
Javi nunca at esperaste danina
no I don't take them off you Says Juani Juani
no que no te las quite Dice Juani Juani
I'll give them to you if you want them but I
yo te las doy si tú las quieres pero yo
already believe
ya creo
that I already believe that man Karime has
que yo ya creo que hombre Karime te ha
made you a member welcome Karime to the Channel
hecho miembro bienvenida Karime al Canal
I hope you
Espero que te
like it they remove your amidal  and outside I
guste te quitan las amidal y fuera yo
think so
creo que sí
eh I think so eh that I
eh yo creo que sí eh que
definitely have to look for the
indiscutiblemente tengo que buscar la
date and do it eh There's no more there's no more
fecha y hacerlo eh No hay más no hay más
turning around in the end there's going to
vuelta al final haby a
happen it's every month
pasar es que es cada mes
dude it's every [ __ ] month every [ __ ] month
tío es que es cada [__] mes cada [__]
bad dude you don't fail month month and a half I
mes malo tío no fallas mes mes y medio
was sick in Hong Kong in Hong Kong eh
estuve malo en Hong Kong en Hong Kong eh
in Hong Kong what was it like in
en Hong Kong qué es lo que fue en
Thailand I was good but in Hong Kong
Tailandia Estuve bien pero en Hong Kong
eh In the morning at Disney it sprinkled Okay
eh Por la mañana de Disney chispeó Vale
and not sprinkle eh I mean sprinkle it rained a
y n chispear eh o sea chispear llovió un
little nothing sprinkled okay while
poquito nada chispeo vale mientras que
we were in the queue for the tickets
estábamos en la cola de las entradas
for the park to open then
para que abriera el parque después
during the day it didn't rain it was time to get
durante el días no lluvió fue el tiempo
in And shortly after entering also you can
de entrar Y al poco de entrada además se
see in the video no
ve en el vídeo no
and And from then on at night bad from
y Y a partir de ahí por la noche malo a
then on at night bad bad and I
partir de ahí por la noche malo malo y
was the whole trip in Hong Kong
ya estuve todo el viaje de Hong kongo
the whole trip in Hong Kong bad
tod el viajes de Hong Kong malo
buying
comprando
ibuprofens I felt bad my
ibuprofenos me encontraba mal me dolía
throat hurt How long has that been going what day
la garganta Cuánto hace eso qué día
was I in Disney at the beginning of at the
estve en Disney a principio de a
beginning of
principio de
March a month a month and a half every  month and a
marzo un mes un mes y medio cada mes y
half every month and a half Look it
medio cada mes y medio Mira
was
fue el
Monday I don't know if it was Monday Tuesday
lunes no sé si fue el lunes martes
we went early in the morning to the beach
fuimos por la mañana temprano a la playa
and it was a little chilly well it's already bad that was
y hacía fresquito pues ya está
Monday morning we
malo eso fue el lunes por la mañana
went to the beach there was a little
fuimos a la playa haía un poco de
chilly badly my throat and I've been
fresquito malo de la garganta y llevo
bad all week all
toda la semana malo toda la
week a kiss
semana un beso
garvi man I'm here for I'm here to
garvi tío yo estoy para yo estoy para
be here calm to be here at
estar aquí tranquilo para estar aquí en
home
casa
calm if it's relative the
tranquilo si es relativo las cuerdas
vocal cords pure potassium pills at the
bucales pastillitas de potasio puro en
pharmacy
farmacia
miraculous well stop me from using the remedy
milagroso bueno dejarme de remedio
because there's nothing to do There's nothing
porque no hay nada que hacer No hay nada
to do Oh my God but it's just
que hacer Ay Dios mío pero es que lo
not to go out eh it's just
suyo es que no salga eh lo suyo es que
not to go out
no salga
man the truth eh it's just not to go out damn
tío la verdad eh lo suyo es que no salga
why go out man if on top of that it's
[__] para qué salir tío si es que además
become Cano eh just as
se ha convertido en Cano eh tal y como
such and as I go out just as I'm going
tal y como salgo tal y como voy a alguna
somewhere things happen the gossip was
parte pasan cosas estaba el salseo
stopped not the next thing paradise imo
parado no lo siguiente paradís imo pasan
things happen it doesn't fail eh I went
cosas no falla eh Me fui
to Well I had to come twice sisuka
a Bueno tuve que venir dos veces sisuka
Thank you very much sweetheart a round of applause
Muchísimas gracias corazón un aplauso
for sisuca
para sisuca
who came twice first
que venir dos veces primer
eh because he had arranged to meet a
eh porque había quedado con un
journalist from  Thailand to do the
periodista de Tailandia para hacer el
live not on the main channel and I
directo no en el canal principal y me
had taken the laptop to do it and
había llevado el portátil para hacerlo y
I left it here in the rush I left it
me lo dejé aquí con la prisas me lo dejé
at the entrance of the house okay anyway it's okay
en la entradita de casa vale total dio
nothing happens I'm going there in a
No pasa nada voy para allá en un
moment and I came to do live no and the
momento y vine a hacer directo no y a la
next morning a deep throat and never
siguiente una garganta profunda y nunca
Better
Mejor
said the next throat a
dicho a la garganta siguiente una
deep throat he tells me
garganta profunda me dice
Ha Well I don't know if it was the morning noon it was
Ja Bueno no sé si era la mañana mediodía
I think it was noon it was noon just getting
era yo creo que era mediodía era
up but noon maybe
mediodía recién levantado pero mediodía
and well it wasn't that much just
mejor y me bueno tampoco era tan recién
getting up of course it was more like
levantado claro era era más tirando para
noon around 1 at maybe I don't know I don't
el mediodía para la 1 a las do a lo
remember okay he tells me
mejor no sé no me acuerdo vale me dice
Javi I have a huge candy for you
Javi tengo un caramelito para ti
I say what's up they send it to me And they tell me
tremendo digo qué pasa me lo mandan Y me
Well I see the video they don't send me
Bueno veo el vídeo no me mandan el vídeo
this video of Gemita not this click of
este de gemita no el click este de
Gemita and of course when I see it when I
gemita y claro yo cuando lo veo cuando
see the click of Gemita the first thing I
veo el click de gemita lo primero que
think is when they send me a clip that you can
pienso es cuando me mandan un clip que
see is from a Stream I say this is
se ve que es de un Stream digo esto es
a clip that they deleted from the live
un clip que han borrado del directo
directly something happened they
directamente ha pasado algo lo han
deleted it and what I expected was that
borrado y yo lo que me esperaba era que
suddenly it would appear  gref who was
de repente iba a aparecer gref que de
suddenly going to appear as she was
repente iba a aparecer como estaba ella
doing something on the phone and the
le haciendo algo en el teléfono y la
mini When old tasty to
mini Para cuando viejo sabroso
do It has to be done a kiss Thank you very much I
hacer Hay que hacerlo un beso Muchas
have to do it no but no
gracias tengo que hacerlo no pero fuera
jokes eh We have to do it now eh the mini eh
coñas eh Hay que hacerlo ya eh la mini
Total what I say Well I see the click and I don't
eh Total que digo Bueno veo el clic y no
realize what's happening and I tell that
me doy cuenta de lo que pasa y le digo a
person what's going on with this
persona que qué es lo que pasa con este
click Because also the person sent me
click Porque además la persona me mandó
the click with a lot of mystery eh I mean he
el click con mucho misterio eh o sea me
also sent it to me by WhatsApp with this thing that
lo mandó además por WhatsApp con esta de
you can only open it once damn Calm down calm down Calm down
de que solo lo puedes abrir una vez dio
boy Calm down calm down with
tranquilo chico Tranquilo tranquilo con
the file Total that when I see the clip
el archivo Total que cuando veo el clip
for the first time I don't realize what what's going on he
por primera vez no me doy cuenta de lo
says damn look
que que es lo que pasa dice [__] fíjate
behind and when I look behind I say
detrás y cuando veo detrás digo
wow I already saw it I saw it what a catch
[__] Ya lo vi ya lo vi vaya pillada
what I didn't know was
vaya pillada ya lo que no sabía yo era
that there was a Lore behind it in which the
que había un Lore detrás en el que ya el
rebor fandom already
fandom de rebor
suspected due to some other indications
sospechaba por algunos otros indicios de
that rebor had something with this girl okay
que rebor tenía algo con esta chica vale
In fact rebor rebor denied it
De hecho rebor rebor lo negaba
okay in the face of speculation
vale ante las especulaciones
rebor I am  single okay so that it's
rebor yo estoy soltero vale para que te
clear to you since so many people are
quede claro ya que tanta gente está te
I'm telling you, reborn is
lo digo yo reborn está
single this was incredible I mean the
soltero esto Fue increíble o sea el
bastard from the south
cabrón del sur
eh Of course because when they sent me
eh Claro porque a mí cuando me mandaron
the
el
click man I had the cli 4 hours before the
click tío yo tuve el cli 4 horas antes
uncle's tet shur okay but I took it
del tet del tío shur vale pero cogí
and took it and sent it to the editor and it
y cogí y se lo mandé al editor además
also seems to me that I regretted
también me parece me arrepentí luego de
having uploaded it to the main Channel man, I
haberlo subido al Canal principal tío el
uploaded the video to the main Channel and it
vídeo lo subí al Canal principal y no
wasn't a video for the main channel it
era un vídeo para el canal principal no
wasn't one of the videos that I'm
era un vídeo de los los que estoy
uploading to the main Channel but of course it was going to
subiendo al Canal principal pero claro
be a bomb and I knew it was going to
como iba a ser una bomba y sabía que iba
be viral but then it didn't
a ser viral que luego a mí no me
work for me it got 15,000 or 17,000 views
funcionó me cogió 15000 o 17000 visitas
something like that is what it has it was more viral
algo así es lo que tiene fue más viral
on Twitter Okay
en Twitter Vale
and man, the clip I assumed
y y tío el clip yo daba por hecho que
was removed from everywhere and I
estaba eliminado de todas partes y
say When I upload the video to YouTube at the same
digo Cuando suba el vídeo a YouTube a la
time I upload it on
vez lo subo en
Twitter okay so I took it
Twitter vale entonces cogí
and while the editor that was going to the
y mientras que el editor eso iba para la
salsera it was a video that was going to the
salsería es era un vídeo que iba para la
salsera But well I got carried away
salsería Pero bueno me vine arriba
when they made the thumbnail  I saw the
cuando me hicieron la miniatura vi la
thumbnail that was very pretty it doesn't
miniatura que estaba muy guapa no
fit with the rest of the content and
desencaja con el resto del contenido y y
I say wow Well I don't know if it's for the
digo [__] Pues no sé si es para el
main page because then however
principal porque luego sin embargo
When I did the exclusive of
Cuando hice la exclusiva de la ruptura
Auron's breakup and I saw yes I did it in the
de de auron y ví sí que la hice en la
salsera and I regretted not having it
salsería y me arrepentí de no haberla he
in the main page but why very
en el principal pero por qué muy
simple Because because the exclusive of
sencillo Porque porque la exclusiva de
Auron And villin did get me visits I don't know
auron Y villin sí me Pillo visita no sé
if it has 80 90,000 you know So what is it that
si tiene 80 90.000 sabes Entonces qué es
I don't like about this one
lo que qué es lo que no me gusta de este
of rebor and gata that has 17,000
del de rebor y gata que tiene 17000
You know why then the video It is well
Sabes porque luego el vídeo Está bien
edited it is a quick bomb it is a
editado es una bomba rápida es un es un
gossip it is a it is a quick bomb and
salseo es es una es una bomba rápida y
the problem is that it has no visits If it had had
el problema es que no tiene visita Si
100,000 visits it wouldn't
hubiera tenido tenido 100000 visitas no
bother us okay But the truth is that
nos molestaba vale Pero la verdad es que
the main channel man we have revived
el canal principal tío lo hemos revivido
eh absolutely almost all the videos
eh absolutamente casi todos los vídeos
more than 100,000 okay And if not then 50 60
más de 100.000 vale Y si no pues 50 60
70 80 okay or rather  200 300,000 eh eh And of
70 80 vale o sea 200 300.000 eh eh Y
course now it shocks me to have a video there
claro ahora me choca tener ahí un vídeo
with 17,000 But oh well, it's okay, not all of them are going to
con 17.000 Pero bueno no pasa nada todos
work okay And then the
no van a funcionar vale Y luego los
live shows are the same eh I mean the series of
directos igual eh o sea la serie de
live shows that we're doing about the
directo que estamos haciendo del caso
Daniel Sancho case
Daniel Sancho
eh spectacular eh neither dicks these
eh espectacular eh ni ni pollas estas
vertical guys nor [ __ ] Eh more than 100,000
del vertical ni [__] Eh más de 100000
views In total, what I believed
visitas Total que yo lo que me creía
apart from the fact that I believed that
aparte de que me creía que iba a
the video was going to break that nobody had the
reventarme el vídeo que nadie tenía el
clip like they sent it to me with that
clip como me lo mandaron con ese
mystery like they sent it to me with that
misterio como me lo mandaron con ese
mystery I mean wow eh
misterio digo [__] eh marcazo de agua
watermark watermark and there were a lot of people on
marcazo de agua y había mucha gente en
Twitter throwing me ge with the
Twitter tirándome ge con el tema de la
watermark issue I said it in the video the
marca de agua lo dije en el vídeo el
other day let's see eh the videos on my three
otro día a ver eh los vídeos de mis tres
channels for a while have had an aesthetic
canales de un tiempo llevan una estética
in that sense when I click that they
en ese sentido cuando pongo clic que no
are not mine
son míos
and I mark
e marco modo
mirror mode silences in between removed okay
espejo silencios por medio quitado vale
with a touch of speed also
con un toquecito de velocidad también
sometimes it has some
algunas veces lleva algún filtro de
image filter the watermark Final South to sel
imagen la marca de agua Sur final a sel
in its two masculine ordinal indicator
en su dos indicador ordinal masculino
rioyo  your final answer the sel in your
rioyo su rpta final las sel en su
secondary today remind me please
secundario hoy recordármelo porfa
remind me if my voice holds we
recordármelo si me aguanta la voz lo
see everything everything everything today okay
vemos todo todo todo hoy vale
eh what I was saying okay
eh lo que os iba diciendo vale
basically all the clips all everything
básicamente todos los clips todos todos
okay whatever even Even the
vale de lo que sea incluso Incluso el
delos tells me many times [ __ ]
delos me dice muchas veces cabrón por
why do you put me in mirror mode and he puts
qué me pones modo espejo y le pone Por
Why do you put it in mirror mode and put that
qué le pones modo espejo y le pones esa
watermark on the podcast and I'm not going to
marca de agua al podcast y yo no te voy
throw it at anyone it's that I don't care it's that it
a tirar a nadie es que me da igual es
has that aesthetic and sometimes I
que lleva esa estética y alguna veces se
even put it on a clip of mine at least
lo pongo incluso a clip mío por lo menos
the frame at least the frame okay if
el marco por lo menos el marco vale si
you notice in the three channels it has
os dais cuenta en los tres canales tiene
a frame okay that what I try to make it
un marco vale que que que intento que
go with the theme of the channel or the
vaya con la temática del canal O del
video okay the ones on the main channel go
vídeo vale los del Canal principal van
with the theme of the video and the ones from the
con la temática del vídeo y los del los
kids' newscast Like
del noticiero de chavales Como así como
a video game no and the ones from telesalseo it's
un videojuego no y los de telesalseo es
like the test card no
como la la carta de ajuste no
and it has several reasons eh First of all it
e tiene varios motivos eh En primer
's the issue of the videos being
lugar es el tema de que los vídeos estén
protected in compliance with the regulations And if
protegidos cumpliendo la normativa Y si
someone decides to report it or whatever it
alguien le da por reportar o lo que sea
will be thrown out  back
se lo va a echap atrás
YouTube and on the other hand if there is any
YouTube y por otro lado si hay algún
clip that they take from my channels
clip que lo sacan de mi de mis canales
then the watermark of my channel will be there I mean if there are no
pues va a estar la marca de agua de mi
more if there are
canal O sea si es que no hay más si es
no more okay or the clip because because they had
que no hay más vale o sea el clip porque
taken it okay But if it happens
porque lo habían cogido vale Pero si
and it happens many times I mean It
llega a ser y pasa muchas veces o sea
happens many times many times that maybe the
Pasa muchísimas veces muchísimas veces
only thing that exists is the
que a lo mejor nada más que existe el
clip is on my channel And what
clip está en mi canal Y qué es lo que
happens uh
pasa
that when they take the clip then
eh que cuando cogen el clip pues Sale
the name of my channel appears Oh dead
sale el nombre de mi canal Ay muerto
hungry I don't know no if dead hungry nothing yes
hambre no sé no si muerto hambre nada si
dead hungry absolutely for nothing
muerto hambre absolutamente para nada
eh 15 and a half million visits
eh 15 millones y medio de visitas
we have had on the main channel this month
llevamos en el canal principal este mes
eh I don't know if in telesalseo there are 3 million
eh No sé si en telesalseo van 3 millones
and here here I don't know how many here
y en aquí aquí no sé cuánt van aquí
how many there are
cuántos van
4.700000 Javi I come here in peace
4.700000 Javi vengo aquí en son de paz
a hug Thank you very much eh I don't know
un abrazo Muchas gracias eh No sé
honestly I have no idea 15
sinceramente no tengo ni idea 15
million main channel it's not about
millones canal principal no se trata de
dead hungry or anything but that
muerto de hambre ni nada sino que eso
way I mean if they take click from here
así O sea si si se cogen click de aquí
from my channel Or for whatever reason there is a
de mi canal O por lo que sea hay un
click that  it can only be rescued on
click que solamente se puede rescatar en
my channel because the watermark will appear,
mi canal pues va a aparecer la marca de
so if it doesn't, it doesn't have
agua o sea si es que no tampoco tiene
much more history in this case What
mucha más más historia en este caso Cuál
was my mistake that I made, man, because I
es el error mío que cometí tío porque me
thought I had it, okay, I thought I
creía que lo tenía yo vale me creía que
had it, of course, they sent it to me
lo tenía yo claro es que me lo mandaron
with so much mystery that I thought
con tanto misterio que me creía que lo
I had it and my mistake here was that
tenía yo y mi mi error aquí fue que
apart from the fact that I was going to make the video
aparte de que yo fuese a hacer el vídeo
on YouTube, okay, I should have put
en YouTube vale tenía que haber puesto
the cli on
el cli en
Twitter Well, you know when I saw that
Twitter Bueno pues sabéis cuándo vi que
uncle shur put the tweet 15 you can
el tío shur puso el tweet 15 lo podéis
check it 15 minutes
comprobar 15 minutos
before 15 minutes before
antes 15 minutos antes de que se
my video was published by the main guy
publicara el vídeo mío del principal tío
and I had it like three or four hours before it
y yo lo tenía como tres o cu horas antes
took the editor to have the
que tardó el editor en tenerme el
video if I had uploaded it to Twitter
vídeo si yo lo hubiera subido a Twitter
man and it's not going to happen to me again when I
tío y ya no me va a pasar más cuando
have something like that I'm going to take it and I'm
tenga una cosa así la voy a [__] y la
going to put it on Twitter which is faster
voy a poner en Twitter que es más rápido
okay it's
vale es más
faster than the YouTube video because the
rápido que el vídeo de YouTube porque el
YouTube video Unless it's a video of
vídeo de YouTube Como no sea un vídeo de
this that I make with my cell phone
esto que os hago yo con el móvil
quickly and it doesn't go through
rápidamente y no pase
editing there's no way it will be fast There's
edición no hay manera de que sea rápido
no
No hay
way  there's no way it's fast and I
manera no hay manera de que sea rápido y
could have had it man But oh well it doesn't matter
pude haberlo tenido tío Pero bueno da
you'll see your [ __ ] and and it happens to me for having
igual verás tú [__] y y me pasa por
wanted to have it on
por haberlo querido tener en
YouTube exactly Christopher we don't
YouTube exactamente Christopher no nos
need more views we do
hacen falta más visitas no nos hacen
n't need more money we're doing well The important thing is to should have given the news to us first [Music] well This seems spectacular to me eh Now let's comment on everything although I already commented on this about AR Juan I already commented on it I'm not going to
de lo de AR Juan Ya lo comenté no lo voy
comment on it again I've already told you my
a volver a comentar Ya os lo he dicho mi
thread has almost 12 million views and
hilo tiene casi 12 millones de visitas y
the inco Sky one
el de inco Sky
but but it's after the news it's not
pero pero es posterior a la noticia no
the cli one as such
es el del cli como tal
e
e
Ah this girl didn't get involved with the
Ah la chica esta no se metió con la
death of Juan's sister okay No it's not
muerte de de la hermana de Juan vale No
debatable she got involved with Ari I mean
no es debatible se metió con Ari O sea
the girl made fun of Ari I mean the one who
la chica se burló de Ari O sea la que
was unfortunate was Ari okay I mean the thing
fue desafortunada fue Ari vale o sea lo
with Juan and Ari Gameplay here attacking
de Juan y Ari Gameplay aquí atacando a
rebor for the girl or because he didn't want to
rebor por la chica o porque no la quiso
kick her out apart from what it
echar aparte que me
seems to me Let's see let's talk clearly let's talk clearly would
parece A ver vamos a hablar claro vamos
you kick your girlfriend from your server
claro tú echarías de tu servidor a tu
not this  it's like when they threw
novia no esto es como cuando le echaban
Auro in play in the face that villin
a Auro en play el en cara que que villin
had the Partner as soon as it
tuviera el Partner nada más
started it's like m Sorry of course or
iniciar es como m Perdona pues claro o
like e in jun no that I gave him the pannor
como e en jun no que yo le di el pannor
that I wanted of
que me dio la gana
course what is there to have studied to have been
claro qué es lo que hay haber estudiado
born to have been born in another in
haber nacido haber nacido en otro en
another womb but it is what there is I mean
otro seno pero es que es lo que hay O
if there is no more okay now
sea si es que no hay más vale ahora lo
about karches man karches with all the
de karches hombre karches con todo el
love eh with all the love carch that it's over
cariño eh con todo el cariño carch que
eh that it's over our our
ya pasó eh que ya pasó nuestro nuestro
pique but you didn't like the
pique pero que no te gustaba nada el
gossip at all or people getting into your
salseo ni que se metieran en tu vida
personal life or the gossip about relationships and about
personal ni el salseo sobre relaciones y
this and that
sobre tal y sobre cual
ehaa you did like this this gossip
ehaa este este salseo sí te gustó
eh carch did like this gossip
eh Este salseo sí le gustó a carch
eh
eh
and who else this one too that this one did
e y quién más este también que a este
n't like the gossip either okay this
tampoco le gustaba el salseo vale este
gossip Uf poop poop unless I
el salseo Uf caca caca a no ser que lo
can control it poop poop Okay and nothing well
pueda controlar caca caca Vale y y nada
six or Canon six or Canon the truth is well
pues seis o Canon seis o Canon la verdad
look precisely I'm going to look at
pues mira precisamente voy a ver el hilo
incai's thread which is more or less  10 million
incai que es más o menos 10 millones de
thread views 59000 likes the whole
visita hilo 59000 likes toda la polémica
Juan Guarnizo controversy and Gameplay against Rebon
de Juan guarnizo y Gameplay contra rebon
Gata well I said I'm not going to
gata bueno Esto he dicho que no lo voy a
comment on this
comentar
Eh I'm not going to comment on this because I already
Eh Esto no lo voy a comentar porque ya
commented on it the other
lo comenté el otro
day I already commented on it the other day
día Ya lo comenté el otro día
come on let's comment on the
venga vamos a comentar el de la
stalker let's
acosadora a
see Ugh I don't know if I'm going to last long
ver Uf no sé yo si voy a aguantar mucho
eh me putting the spine rp scam the
eh yo poniendo la estafa de spine rp los
friendships and relationships between Rebor and
amiguismos y relaciones entre rebor y
Gata this would be someone pleas in the
gata este sería algui pleas en la
evening I'm literally going to last 3
velada yo literalmente voy a durar 3
seconds and I don't care But how do you see it
segundos y me la pela Pero cómo lo veis
the look of the presenter of
el look de presentadora de
rounds for the
rondas para el estilo de
fighting style is a good outfit to go to a
pelea es un buen outfit para ir a un
funeral it is a good outfit we
funeral es un buen outfit esto lo
discussed this at the time eh The thing is
comentamos en su día eh Lo que pasa que
I didn't know who this girl was And I still do
yo no sabía quién era esta chica Y sigo
n't know, I mean I still don't
sin saberlo o sea Sigo sin
know are you going to
saberlo vas a
fight understand the reference is to
pelear entiendan la referencia sea para
make fun of the death of
burlando de la muerte de la hermana de
Juan's sister for me he is making fun of how
Juan para m se está burlando de lo
unfortunate it
desafortunada que
was that you were disrespectful
fue que tu una falta de respeto fue
exactly
exactamente
burying my
enterrando a mi
sister-in-law being such a fake
cuñada siendo una persona tan falsa de
two-faced person that she even asked Juan and Ari to
doble cara que les pedía a Juan y Ari
participate in her
hasta participar en sus
events nothing to do with it absolutely nothing
eventos nada que ver absolutamente nada
to do with it
que
I would have liked to participate even
ver me hubiera gustado participar aún
so I'm sure it's going great you're worth a
así estoy segura que va genial vales
lot
mucho
u said about doxxing I took it and uploaded a
u dije lo de doxear cogí y subí un
Twitter apologizing because I had
Twitter disculpándome porque ahí habí
screwed up this is humor and without saying names
cagado esto es humor y sin decir nombres
if they take it personally Jai did you see that the
si se dan por aludidos Jai viste que la
girl is only fan yes I had it commenting
chica se only fan sí lo tuve comentando
But well eh that in the end m I tell you what I've
Pero bueno eh eso al final m os digo lo
always told you I mean eh that's a
que siempre os he dicho o sea eh eso es
couple's thing yes yes you yes yes you
cosa de la pareja si si tú lo si si tú
have accepted it I don't know I mean me
lo tienes aceptado yo que sé o sea yo
For example I wouldn't put up with that in a
Por ejemplo yo no aguantaría eso en una
couple I
pareja yo
eh but I don't criticize whoever does it or
eh pero yo no critico a quien lo haga ni
whoever doesn't I mean you're not doing
quien no lo haga O sea no estás haciendo
anything wrong if you do hly fan it's another
nada malo si haces hly fan es otro
content okay that is consumed and And well there have to be
contenido vale que se consume y Y bueno
people who do it okay
pues tiene que haber gente que lo haga
And if you and if your partner has
vale Y si tú y si tu pareja lo tiene
assumed it and seems
asumido y le parece
fine to him I wouldn't put up with it eh for many
bien Yo no lo soportaría eh por muchos
reasons I'm not going to get involved now But
motivos no me voy a enrollar ahora Pero
for many reasons and it's not even  possessive
por muchos motivos y no es ni posesivo
or machismo or anything like that, I mean,
ni machismo ni nada por el estilo o sea
for me there are things that have no no there's
eh yo para mí hay cosas que tiene no no
nothing wrong with gebra, I mean, you
no tiene nada de malo gebra o sea no
're not hurting anyone you can be
estás haciendo daño nadie se lo puedes
doing it to your partner if your
estar haciendo a tu pareja si a tu
partner is bothered but if your partner is not
pareja le molesta pero si a tu pareja no
bothered Well everything's perfect I mean yes yes
le molesta Pues todo perfecto O sea si
your partner Eh doesn't care I mean if
si tu pareja Eh no le importa o sea si
you know if you know your partner and
tú conoces a si tú conoces a tu pareja y
your partner does it and you accept it
ya tu pareja lo hace y tú lo aceptas
perfect but me For example, I would
perfecto pero yo Por ejemplo yo no lo
obviously not accept that
aceptaría evidentemente yo eso de que
a person can have certain
una persona pueda tener ciertas
photographs of me of my partner, well no the
fotografía de mi de mi pareja pues no la
truth is something that I prefer to just
verdad es una cosa que prefiero solo
enjoy it myself and for it to be part of
disfrutarlo yo y que sea parte de
our intimacy as a couple you
nuestra intimidad de pareja
understand it's my opinion okay I mean that they
me entiendes es mi opinión vale o sea
can, they can pay
que le que le puedan que le puedan pagar
my partner to have that photograph well it's
a a mi pareja para tener esa fotografía
not worth it now well that whoever
pues no vale ahora bien que quien lo
does it because they think it's right and has another
haga porque le parezca bien Y tenga otra
opinion well it doesn't seem bad to me Neither
opinión pues no me parece mal Tampoco
because you're not hurting anyone, you're not there, you're not
porque no estás haciendo daño a nadie no
messing with anyone, you
está no estás metiéndote con nadie no
're not doing anything illegal so
estás haciendo nada ilegal entonces
no problem with whoever does it
ningún problema con quien lo haga
simply that I, I would not assume it in
simplemente que yo yo no lo asumiría en
a relationship it's
una relación
not my
no es mi
blame And if what happened happened and there was funa
culpa Y si pasó lo que pasó y hubo funa
and there was a meme I wasn't the one who participated I just
y hubo meme yo no era participé yo solo
laughed at a Twitter meme who
me reído de un meme de Twitter quien la
screwed up at that moment wasn't me and I repeat
[__] en ese momento no fui yo y repito
everything was
todo fue
Ari it was
Ari fue
Ari my goodness But what a catch
Ari madre mía Pero qué pillada
eh my goodness what a historic catch eh
eh madre mía qué pillada más histórica
who knows a fan should know that they are
quién se un fan debe saber que está
exposed I have many reasons I
expuesto Es que tengo muchos motivos
have many reasons why I would not
tengo muchos motivos para que yo no lo
accept it in that one not only
aceptase en esa ya no solamente por
because I consider that I do not want
porque yo considere que que no quiero
anyone to have those images of my
que nadie tenga esas imágenes de mi
partner but
pareja sino
because in my case no in my case and in the case of
porque en mi caso no en mi caso y en el
people who have
de en el de las personas que que tengan
children no well not only that there are
hijos no pues ya no solamente que haya
photos of your partner but imagine from
fotos de tu pareja sino imagínate desde
the perspective also of your children that
la perspectiva también de tus hijos que
at school Well maybe there are going to be
en el colegio Pues a lo mejor va a ha
other classmates who are going to have photos
otros compañeros que van a tener fotos
of your mother like that
de tu madre así
and also it is
e además es un
content that cannot be protected from being
contenido que no puede protegerlo a que
leaked okay there are many reasons I
no se filtre vale son muchos motivos Me
could go on and on about that subject but
podría extender mucho con ese tema pero
we have already done it on other occasions man what a catch
ya lo hemos hecho en otras ocasiones tío
eh
vaya pillada eh
[ __ ] but what a catch But how are you not
[__] pero vaya pillada Pero cómo no te
going to
vas a dar
realize that you enter a
cuenta de que entras en un
site and  there's a
sitio y hay una
streamer with a selfie stop doing
streamer con un paro a selfie haciendo
a
un
Stream
Stream
God let's order a cold macho
Dios vamos a pedir un macho frío
cold macho what the [ __ ] is a macho
frío qué [__] es un mache
dude I thought I was buying
tío yo me creía que estaba comprando el
bread of course here I didn't realize when they
pan claro yo aquí no me di cuenta cuando
sent me this click malcha and a
me mandaron este click malcha y un
march What is a
marcha Qué es un
t me here as I saw her I broke my phone
t yo aquí como la vi traste el móvil
because I thought that suddenly an
pues me creía que de repente iba a salir
audio of gr compromising or something was going to come out but
un audio de gr comprometido o algo pero
Andorra is that it is very small
es que andorra es que es muy pequeño
eh they leave there you can't see but they leave they leave
eh se van ahí no se ve pero se van se
then separately eh gata is the biggest
van luego separados eh gata es la mayor
fan of rebor let's
fan de rebor a
see I just met a streamer who
ver acabo de conocer a un streamer que
has little hearts for me I hadn't
me tiene corazoncitos esto no lo había
seen this
visto
we already started talking I'm
ya nos empezamos a hablar Estoy
in love and if I ask him to come to my
enamorada y si le pido que venga a mi
house to play LoL heart heart it
casa a jugar al LoL corazón corazón
would be very
sería muy
hasty
precipitado
right [ __ ] [ __ ] We
verdad
would have to see the date eh To
[__] Habría que ver la fecha eh Para
see if this Wait I'm going to throw I'm going to
ver si esto Espera voy a echar me voy a
throw something with which I'm going to die
echar una cosa con la que voy a morir
this is a Ricky Edi 2.0 eh Let's see I'm going
esto es un Ricky Edi 2.0 eh A ver me voy
to throw something down my throat that I'm going to
a echar una cosa a la garganta que voy a
die okay excuse me for a second  Eh my
morir vale perdonadme un segundo Eh mi
absence you can press the like and give
ausencia podéis pulsar el like y regalar
super chat meanwhile
super chat de
Ah I curse his [ __ ] mother why does
Ah me cago en su [__] madre por qué cuce
that bother so much dude
tanto eso tío
angin it's not going dude
angin no va tío
I
yo
Ah why does that bother so much
Ah por qué cuece tanto
dude very s very simp for his
tío muy s muy simp por su
part I don't think it's simp I think it's
parte yo no creo que sea simp yo creo
a bit let's see here there are two
que es un poco a ver aquí hay dos
options okay
opciones vale
in the end On the one hand
al final Por una parte
and if you move in a circle
e si te mueves en un círculo
of content creators all the
de de creadores de contenido todo el
time Well it's normal that you end up
tiempo Pues es normal que que acabes
having partners who are creators not
teniendo parejas que sean creadores no
of content also who is going to
de contenido además quién se va a
understand each other better not when it comes to having
entender mejor no a la hora de tener
e Many times we have a job that is
e Muchas veces tenemos un trabajo que es
complicated complicated to understand for
complicado complicado de entender para
For our partners Why Because we are
Para nuestras parejas Por qué Porque
very absent many hours I don't know
estamos muy ausentes muchas horas no sé
what then Well it's not bad no
qué entonces Bueno pues no está mal no
another thing
otra cosa
is that she at this moment was not
es que ella en este momento no fuera
known
conocida
and precisely she liked rebor that I do
y precisamente le gustase rebor que yo
n't know what you think but you think
no sé ustedes qué pensáis pero pensáis
With all due respect eh With all due
Con todo el respeto eh Con todo el
respect we are gossiping This is what there is, there is gossip
respeto estamos cotilleando Esto es lo
okay she is an attractive person
vale es una persona atractiva
rebor I mean she is an attractive person that that
rebor o sea es una es una persona
suddenly let's see There is some yes out there the
repente a ver Hay algún sí por ahí la
majority is no no of
mayoría es no
course  to each his own, let's
no claro para gustos colores
see where I'm going with this, well, I'm going to
no a ver a dónde voy con esto pues pues
see, I know, to each his own,
voy a que a ver yo que sé para gustos
but of course it could be the
colores no pero claro que podría ser la
option that she loves you, Rebor. Or it
opción de que a ella le encantas rebor O
could be the option that, but I'm
podría ser la la opción de que pero es
also telling you by putting in the chat
que también os digo poniendo en el chat
home Partner home Partner but home
casa Partner casa Partner pero casa
Partner Put Rebor. Who is Rebor if it's
Partner Pon rebor Quién es rebor si es
a
un
Random, let's see here in these recommendations, it does
Random a ver aquí en estas comendaciones
seem a little uninterested, but
sí que se ve un poco no interesada pero
you also say, good who the [ __ ],
es que también dices tú buen quién [__]
Rebor, not even that she was. You know, I
rebor ni que fuera
think she likes it and she already went
Sabes Yo creo que le gusta y ya se fue
to the bathroom. I think when I come back I'll give her
al baño creo que cuando vuelva le daré
a kiss, kawai, man, but also go on and
un beso kawai tío pero también anda que
tweet these
twitear estas
things, but this. This is real, man. Because
cosas pero esto Esto es real tío Porque
of the account that we're
claro esto de la cuenta que la estamos
reading, wait because maybe they're
leyendo espérate porque capacis nos la
screwing us, eh. Wait, I'm going to
están metiendo eh Espera voy a
check it out, Gamer girl, I mean, how are you going to
comprobarlo chica Gamer o sea cómo vas a
get the user Gamer girl,
[__] el usuario chica
it's impossible to have a user that
Gamer es imposible tener un usuario que
is a Gamer girl, damn this is fake,
sea chica Gamer [__] est esto es falso
dude, this is fake, this is from the
tío esto es falso esto es de la de la
account This Us
cuenta Esta Us
loves this is fake, damn, how have we not
adora esto es fake [__] cómo no lo hemos
thought of it before? Who goes, how does it go?  Who's
pensado antes sea Quién va cómo va Quién
going to get the
va a pillar el
user
usuario chica
Gamer girl there is no user called
Gamer no existe un usuario que se llame
gamer girl
chica gamer
the text is
el texto es
edited it's an account that I had
editado es una cuenta que tenía
before I don't
antes no me lo
believe it let's see I don't
creo a ver no me lo
believe it there is a Gamer girl user
creo hay un usuario chica Gamer
caught This is not real
cogido Esto no es real
eh This is not real
eh Esto no es real
dude let's see wait wait wait
tío a ver espera Espera
Warning if you are an obsessive gamer
espera Warning si eres un gamer obsesivo
don't watch this video let's
no mires este vídeo
see he'll set it up for a while but the whole
ya a ver nos la colo un rato pero todo
time he can't set it up for us
el rato no puede colarnos
dude a thread with a million
la [__] tío un hilo con un millón de
visits with an account
visitas con cuenta
is or rather it's fake the
está o sea es falsa la
screenshot is fake the
captura es falsa la
screenshot of course like that how the [ __ ] is someone
captura claro asía yo cómo [__] alguien
going to
va a
post it says dude South with Jerry you with the
poner dice tío Sur con Jerry tú con la
Gamer girl No because no because look
chica Gamer No porque no porque mira
nothing I was reading I told you eh
nada estaba leyendo te he dicho eh
stay still This is not
quieto parado Esto no es
real Look at the date of the tweets there is no date there is
real Mira la fecha de los twet es que no
no date even
hay fecha es que no hay fecha siquiera
on the
de los
tweets
twit
Ah you mean this already but this could
Ah te refieres a esto ya pero esto puede
belong to a screenshot and that's it but
pertenecer a una captura y ya está pero
anyway look it's not only that it
de todas maneras que mira no solamente
belongs to a screenshot It's that
es que pertenezca a una captura Es que
this this logo this little symbol that you
esto este logotipo este simbolito que
are here below because the 10
estáis aquí abajo porque lo de los 10
seconds thing could  pass that people take
segundos puede pasar que coja la gente
the screenshot at the moment in case someone
la captura al momento por si alguien lo
deletes it and that's it no and the screenshot exists
borra y ya está no y existe la captura
But this Only appears to the person
Pero esto Solo le aparece a la persona
who writes it the
que lo escribe el
Twin this this little symbol here only
Twin esto este simbolito de aquí solo le
appears to the person who writes it man I mean so that so that
aparece a la persona que lo escribe tío
you can see the
o sea para que para que tú veas la
information what you can trust the
información lo que te puede fiar de la
information from this Twitter account
información de esta cuenta de Twitter
which is an account at the end of harassment man I
que es una cuenta al final de acoso tío
mean we gave it I say go on I'm going to
o sea le hemos dado digo anda voy a
take it from there we're going to read nothing eh it is what it is it is what it
[__] de ahí vamos a leer nada eh es lo
is eh so that you can see what
que es es lo que es eh para que veáis lo
you can trust anything
que os podéis fiar de cualquier cosa de
from that
de esa cuenta de
harassment account check it with the wave Machine No
acoso compruébalo con el wave Machine No
but if there are no more if there are no
pero si es que no hay más si es que no
more my goodness then look at you a
hay más madre mía pues fíjate tú un
million visits eh A million
millón de visitas eh Un millón de
people who will have believed those
personas que se habrán creído esas
conversations those
conversaciones esos
twi anyway well and here what I have been able to
twi en fin bueno y aquí lo que he podido
verify
comprobar
is good These are more indications not that they
es bueno Estos son más indicios no de
live together and so on
que viven juntos y
now You're going to see how they
demás ahora Vais a ver cómo se
act You're going to see they don't respect the
actúa Vais a verlo no respetan la
regulations perfect [ __ ] Javi
normativa perfecto de [__] madre Javi no
you can't give credibility to this  sick woman who
puedes darle credibilidad a esta enferma
dreams No but if it wasn't to give it
que sueña No pero si no era por darle
credibility it was because it was the thread
credibilidad si era porque era el hilo
that was there because the inai talked about
que había porque el inai hablaba de lo
Juan and I say Ah well I'm going to read that
de Juan y digo Ah pues voy a leer ese
thread I understand that since it's not about
hilo entiendo que al no tratarse de
Dallas Well maybe it would be
Dallas Pues a lo mejor sería información
more or less information but of course I understand that
más o menos pero claro entiendo que no
in the end she uses these things to
e que al final utiliza estas cosas para
gain repercussions to continue talking
ganar repercusión para seguir hablando
about Dallas or something like that not to
de Dallas o algo por el estilo no para
throw [ __ ] at Dallas and
tirarle [__] a Dallas y
and and I think that this cat girl
y y creo que es que la chica esta gata
at some point has defended Dallas
en algún momento ha defendido a Dallas
so that's
entonces por ahí va
probably where she's going You're going to see how she
seguramente Vais a ver cómo se
acts You're going to see they don't respect the
actúa Vais a verlo no respetan la
regulations perfect [ __ ] great I'm going
normativa perfecto de [__] madre Te voy
to stick one up your ass that you're going to freak out
a meter una por el culo que vas a flipar
[ __ ] and I'll
cabrón y os
explain you see yourselves going to
explico os veis a
eat 60 months in
comer 60 meses de
jail because since when has a
cárcel porque desde cuandoo se roba una
[ __ ] store been robbed with a
[__] tienda con un
jugular months that you shut your [ __ ] mouth
jugular meses que te ces la [__] boca
now You're going to see how she
ahora Vais a ver cómo se
acts well This is
actúa bueno Esto es lo de
ant Ho dude really eh I mean fatal fatal
ant Ho tío de verdad eh o sea fatal
fatal any streamer who
fatal fatal cualquier streamer que
streams on another server today goes
Stream en otro servidor a día de hoy va
against the streamer regulations Period and is
contra la normativa de streamers Punto y
automatically excluded from the program  from
automáticamente excluido del programa de
content creator Spain himself npc Play
content creator Spain mismísimo npc Play
shared such a decision this
compartieron tal decisión este
thought of my server only
pensamiento de mi server solo
exclusivity such I don't know what I don't
exclusividad tal no sé qué no lo
share that for me it is very 2020
comparto eso yo para mí es muy de 2020
honestly why does that happen
sinceramente por qué pasa eso pues
because the owner of the server has decided to
porque el dueño del servidor ha decidido
do that and what do you think about that it
hacer eso y qué opinas sobre eso a mí me
seems to me like, well, not bad I
parece una en plan o sea no a mal me
mean I wouldn't do it it seems to me like I don't
refiero que yo no lo haría me parece o
think it's right that people do
sea no me parece bien que la gente haga
those things on the servers Why
esas cosas en los servidores Por qué
Because that is very 2020 dude it's very
Porque eso es muy de 2020 tío es muy
2020 and we are in 2024 and things have changed a
2020 y estamos en 2024 y han cambiado
lot Hey and what do you think? Well, it's
mucho las cosas Oye y qué te parece pues
[ __ ] [ __ ] but not bad eh [ __ ]
una [__] [__] pero no a mala eh [__]
the well-liked of these people has no
el bienquisto de esta gente no tiene
limits J corco was also on the
límite J corco también estaba en la
list of those who did not see this with a
lista de los que no vieron esto con
good eye I think that in the end it is
buenos ojo creo que al final es
exclusivity it is something very very big I think
exclusividad es algo muy muy grande creo
that exclusivity is something somewhat
que exclusividad es algo algo sin
meaningless Well in the end this throwing
sentido Bueno al final esto echándole un
in his face a little
poco en cara
eh throwing in his face a little the issue of
eh echándole un poco en cara el tema de
having another other type of
que tuviera otro otro tipo de
behavior another type of measuring stick
comportamiento otro tipo de vara de
No to  the time to sanction gata
medin No a la hora de sancionar a gata
eh regarding Juan and hari is that
eh respecto a lo de Juan y hari es que
regarding Juan and Ari for me no it
respecto a lo de Juan y Ari para mí no
is not at all punishable I mean at what
no es nada sancionable o sea en qué
point is it going to be punishable to make a
momento va a ser sancionable hacer una
joke about something viral that is being
broma sobre una cosa viral que se está
discussed on Twitter because Ari has
comentando en Twitter porque Ari ha
put his foot in it is that it does not make sense
metido la pata es que no tiene sentido
okay then this cli coming from the
vale luego este cli viniendo de la
harassment account Let's see wait pu cap
cuenta de acoso A ver espérate pu capá
the false c
el c falso
also your clothes
también ti ropa
sir Hello I see that It was of no use what
señor Hola veo que De nada sirvió lo que
the r said just because gata refused to go
dijo la r solo porque gata se reusó a ir
to the academy she was the only one so verza it makes
a la academia fue la única tanta verza
you say that she is your partner reja and that We
te da decir que es tu par reja y que la
will have to endure Yes or yes I would
Tendremos que soportar Sí o sí yo
also be ashamed knowing that she
también tendría verguenza sabiendo que
uploaded intimate photos to love that she likes
subió fotos íntimas a love que le gusta
Suck my [ __ ] not moved it Well
Chúpame la [__] no lo movido Pues es
this will be
que esto será
eh It is that this will be false also
eh Es que esto será falso también
probably not I mean this donation It is
probablemente no O sea esta donación Es
true that rebn
verdad que rebón la
received it a you clothes
recibió una ti ropa
sir Hello I see that It was of no use what
señor Hola veo que De nada sirvió lo que
the r said that only
dijo la r que solo
porem was the only one so ashamed of you to
porem fue la única tanta verguenza te da
say that she is your partner and that  We will have to
decir que es tu parja y que la Tendremos
endure if Or yes I would also be
que soportar si O sí yo también tendría
ashamed knowing that she uploaded
verguenza sabiendo que subió fotos
intimate photos that she likes ch the [ __ ] not
íntimas a que le gusta ch la [__] no
moved I just got such a
movido me acaba de dar un cring tan
big cring for the previous message that don't
grande por el mensaje anterior que no
see that if we don't lose such
veas que si no perdemos tan
a look now we don't give a
vistazo ya nois que me la pela
damn This is
[__] Esta es
real it's
real es
real Well rebor has been
real Bueno pues rebor ha estado
responding a little let's not see
respondiendo un poco no vamos a ver qué
what rebor has said trying to clarify the
es lo que ha dicho rebor intenta aclarar
whole cat controversy both parties
toda la polémica de gata ambas partes
have acted badly yesterday rebor
han actuado mal el día de ayer rebor
responded to all the criticism she has
respondió a todas las críticas que ha
received and mainly focusing
recibido y principalmente enfocándonos
on the cat issue and
en el tema de gata y el trato
preferential treatment Let's see let's see the
preferencial A ver vamos a ver lo
first thing but what crazy things I'm reading
primero pero qué locuras Estoy leyendo
man what crazy things I'm reading here man I don't give
tío qué locuras Estoy leyendo aquí tío
a damn about your private life
me importa un cuerno tu vida privada
but defending a person who harasses and
pero defender una persona que acosa y
then plays the victim is the problem this has
después se victimiza es el problema esto
already been discussed with her it has already been
ya se ha hablado con ella ya se ha
discussed with her and I'm going to say something else
hablado con ella y voy a decir otra cosa
There is a list of the amount of aunt stuff
Hay una lista de la cantidad de tía coso
that she also eats I mean there is
que también se se come ella es decir que
a problem here both parties
aquí hay un problema es que ambas partes
have acted badly in that sense it has been
han actuado mal en ese sentido ha sido
a vicious circle in  which Who is
un círculo vicioso en el cual Quién es
a part that goes for this and another part
una parte que va por este y otra parte
that goes for this and so on and it has
que va por este y así sucesivamente y se
become a ball deeve constantly it has
ha hecho una bola deeve constantemente
become a snowball is that it is
se ha hecho una bola de nieve es que es
like this that is wrong I have said that it is
así esto que está mal he dicho que está
wrong [ __ ] at what moment am I
mal [__] en qué momento estoy
justifying don't you hear I am saying that it is
justificando no oyes estoy diciendo que
wrong [ __ ] are you deaf or what and what the
está mal [__] estáis sordos o qué y qué
[ __ ] does there have to be in this guy I
[__] tiene que haber des en esto tío lo
said it is wrong it is wrong In what in what I
he dicho está mal está mal En qué en qué
tell myself guy she comes to say it
yo me lo digo tío ella venga a decirlo
Then it is wrong but she
Entonces es que está mal pero ella
has also received J Yes of course she
también has recibido J Sí por supuesto
has received it or is it not true that I have
que lo ha recibido o no es verdad que he
had to ban even emotes from my
tenido que banear incluso emotes de mi
channel Or is it not true that I have had the TL
canal O no es verdad que he tenido el TL
full of no that is not true no also we have to
lleno de no eso no es verdad no también
be a little fair in life eh let's
hay que ser un poco justos en la vida eh
not get so excited that I have
tampoco nos vengamos tan arriba que haya
done things wrong Yes but there are also other
hecho cosas mal Sí pero también hay otra
people who have also done wrong have
gente que también lo ha hecho mal
also done badly man if we are
también lo ha hecho mal hombre si somos
fair we are really fair we are fair we are
justos somos justos de verdad somos
fair because she started and
justos somos justos porque ella empezó y
what we are 12 years old that we are 12 years old we
qué tenemos 12 años qu tenemos 12 años
cannot mature and understand that it is worth
no podemos madurar y entender que vale
Okay a  snowball has
Okay se ha formado una bola de nieve ha
degenerated more and more Okay what she has
degenerado cada vez más Okay lo que ha
done is wrong Yes but there are also people
hecho está mal Sí pero también hay gente
who have done things that are wrong too okay that
que ha hecho cosas que están mal también
is not justifying it is justice it is
vale eso no es justificar es justicia es
equity Okay he does things wrong he does things
equidad Okay hace cosas mal hace cosas
wrong okay well he stops he stops
mal okay pues se para se para por
completely he stops and something else happens
completo se para y se pasa otra cosa
damn the problem is not Spin It is the lack
[__] el problema no es Spin Es la falta
of respect for your community we eat from
de respeto a tu comunidad comemos de
it for defending your private life and it is not
ella por defender tu vida privada y no
a mistake that You could talk
se trata de un error que Pudiste hablar
to her and fix it it's been three months you
con ella y se arregla son tres meses
could stop this before and You let us
pudiste parar esto antes y Nos dejaste
eat and now be the mockery okay let's see I have
comer y ahora ser la burla vale a ver yo
spoken repeatedly with
he hablado en reiteradas ocasiones con
her that you have not seen it is another
ella que no lo hayáis visto es otra
story but on many occasions I have
historia pero yo en muchas ocasiones le
told her this not this either do not do that do not
he dicho esto no esto tampoco no hagas
do the other many times
eso no hagas lo otro muchas las veces
that I have said it she has been rectifying What
que lo he dicho ha ido rectificando Qué
happens I explain to you I explain okay And there I
pasa os explico os explico vale Y ahí
am entering into topics that I should not
estoy entrando en temas que no debería
agree The problem is that it
entrar de acuerdo El problema es que no
is not a streamer to use, for example I
es un streamer al uso yo por ejemplo
have been for 4 years and logically I have a
llevo 4 años y lógicamente tengo una
way of doing things but when
forma de hacer las cosas pero cuando
someone let me finish let me
alguien dejadme terminar dejadme
finish when a person does not  She's
terminar cuando una persona no está
used to it because she makes mistakes she makes them she keeps
acostumbrada pues comete cagadas las
making them and that's
comete las va cometiendo y punto y ya
it and the things that she's done wrong I've
está y las cosas que ha hecho mal yo lo
been saying heard saying What happens
he ido diciendo oído diciendo Qué pasa
at the moment the temp parameter you
en el momento el temp paramento te
get hot and all that [ __ ] that's not a
calientas y esas [__] que no es una
justification it's not at all but it
justificación no lo es en absoluto pero
is the reality of the facts the
es que es la realidad de los hechos la
truth let's see I'm going to read what she said on
verdad a ver voy a leer que ha dicho en
gok it generates serious doubts for me the criticism
gok a mí me genera dura dudas la crítica
in general at least from my person is
en general al menos desde mi persona es
the fact that a person within the
el hecho de que una persona dentro del
server said something very unpleasant to another
server dijo algo muy desagradable a otra
that clearly is a violation of the rules
que claramente es una falta a las normas
and later that person would seem
y posteriormente esa persona parecería
not to have received any type of
que no hubiera recibido ningún tipo de
sanction dude but what
sanción tío pero que lo que ha dicho
gata said no no it's not
gata no no no es
punishable what gata said is not
sancionable lo que ha dicho gata no es
punishable I mean what's going to be
sancionable O sea qué va a ser
punishable or rather
sancionable o sea
Ari Gameplays puts a post on
Ari Gameplays pone una publicación en
all his networks Look how hot I am and or
todas sus redes Mira qué buena estoy y o
what tits I have what he posted How
qué tetas tengo qué es lo que puso Qué
hot I am or something like that no or what tits I
buena estoy o algo así no o qué tetas
have I don't remember
tengo no me acuerdo
okay a while after Juan put
vale un rato después de que Juan pusiera
a tweet saying I'm going to Colombia that
un tet diciendo me voy a Colombia que ha
my
muerto mi
sister died why do they have to sanction her
hermana por qué tienen que sancionarla a
her because a doll dressed in
ella porque sale una muñeca vestida de
colors and with a shori with a low neckline comes out and
colores y con un shori con un escote y
says Oh look what an outfit so suitable for
diga Ay mira qué traje tan adecuado para
a
un
funeral
funeral Por
Why ah there are many things that
qué ah que hay muchas cosas que hizo
antirol did well
antirol bueno
By
Por
the way I had forgotten to put member mode
cierto se me había olvidado poner modo
you if you are referring to
tú si se refiere a
that I don't know if I'm going to be
eso no sé si voy a
able I don't know if I'm going to be able to continue much longer
poder no sé si voy a poder continuar
with the live eh having had
mucho con el directo eh habiendo haido
an evident preference that gata be a
una preferencia evidente que gata sea
girlfriend of rebor that she be her best friend
novia de rebor que sea su mejor amig
personally I completely care
personalmente me da completamente igual
and I will never I will get into her private life
y jamás Me meteré en su vida privada
because nobody should care but
porque eso nadie debería importar pero
the criticism still has the same
la crítica sigue teniendo el mismo
meaning no matter why what
sentido no importa el por qué lo que
matters is that it would seem that there is
importa es que parecería que sí hay un
preferential treatment But of course there is but of course there is
trato preferencial Pero es que claro que
But
hay pero es que claro que lo hay Pero
how could I not
cómo no iba a ha
see it if she is his
verlo si es su
girlfriend anyway this is salty yes it is a
novia en fin este es salo sí que es un
[Music]
[Música]
little bit for you what the [ __ ] are you
poco per tú qué [__]
are
estás es
[ __ ] No now I'm going to be funned for
[__] No ahora se me va a funar por
having a life but what the [ __ ] do you
tener vida pero tú qué [__] te has
think this is dude Are you crazy or
creído que es esto tío Estás loco o
what the [ __ ] [ __ ] kid We are crazy We are
qué [__] [__] chaval Estamos locos
crazy or what the mother of love
Estamos locos o qué madre del amor
blessed what I'm reading dude of course
bendito lo que estoy leyendo tío claro
[ __ ]
[__]
kid [ __ ] [ __ ] no no Of course totally the rebate the rebound that he got rebor is that they were messing with him basically because Ah so now you have a girlfriend and your girlfriend is this chick and that's why you've been softer on her man Of course obviously anyway
en
[ __ ] I was going to watch the video
[__] iba a ver el vídeo
of I was going to watch the video of
de iba a ver el vídeo de lo de lados de
Claudia Nicolasa's sides but it lasts an
Claudia nicolasa pero es que dura una
hour you and I'm like I am let's see I'm going to
hora tú y estoy como estoy a ver voy a
watch the cat how How long is The cat I'm
ver la gata cóm Cuánto dura de La gata
going to watch the video of
voy a ver el vídeo de la gata de
Rodinger's cat okay about the sides Let's see
rodinger vale sobre lo de lados A ver
There were
Había
people but I understand that no eh I mean there
gente pero entiendo que no eh o sea
were a lot of people who were accusing her
había mucha gente que la estaba acusando
of copying the video from this girl
de copiarle el vídeo a a esta chica a
Claudia Nicolasa okay but I understand that
Claudia nicolasa vale pero entiendo que
one video has nothing to do with the
no tiene nada que ver un vídeo con el
other
otro
no I mean Claudia Nicolas also
no O sea el de Claudia Nicolas tamb se
infiltrates according to the title eh I don't know then
infiltra según el título eh No sé luego
the inside okay infiltrates too
el interior vale se infiltra también
Congratulations on how your
Felicidades por como te está yendo en tu
main channel is doing very good videos hands
canal principal muy buenos vídeos manos
applauding Thank you very much Omega Today there is a
aplaudiendo Muchas gracias Omega Hoy hay
video eh Today there is a
vídeo eh Hoy hay
video let's see it's the same subject And such But
vídeo a ver es el mismo tema Y tal Pero
No no I don't think it's plagiarism as such It would
no no no creo que sea un plagio como tal
be too much of Caro eh on the part of the
Sería mucho de Caro eh por parte de la
cat I mean yes the cat has done it in
gata O sea sí que la gata lo ha hecho en
her time
su tiempo
copying some other video no and such
copiar algún que otro videíto no y tal
No we already talked about it but man copying a
No ya lo hablamos pero hombre copiar un
video of 800,000 views would seem
vídeo de 800,000 visitas me parecería
very
muy
shameless to me apart from that she doesn't have time in three
descarado aparte no le da tiempo en tres
days there were three days of difference between one
días hubo tres días de diferencia de un
video and another Eh So I don't think so eh
vídeo a otro Eh Así que no lo creo eh
But well let's see it apart from that the one
Pero bueno vamos a verlo aparte que el
of The cat lasts 15 minutes 16
de La gata dura 15 minutos 16
minutes I'm sure that
minutos estoy segura de que todo el
everyone has seen videos of llados without
mundo ha visto vídeos de llados sin
internet Look at the other side belly belly
internet Mira al otro lado panza panza
belly mileurista mileurista mileurista
panza mileurista mileurista mileurista
meme it's served By the way she speaks
meme está servido Por su forma de hablar
for the things she says but what's
por las cosas que dice pero qué hay
behind what's behind behind I've
detrás qué hay detrás detrás me he
infiltrated like Thank you Isuka for
infiltrado como Gracias isuka por
appreciating the effort that I'm making I'm
valorar el esfuerzo que estoy haciendo
not going to be able to hold out much longer eh I would
no voy a poder aguantar mucho más eh Me
like to see a couple of
gustaría ver un par de
things to more or less stay up to date
cosas para más o menos quedarnos al día
okay To more or less stay up to date with
vale Para más o menos quedarnos Al Día
everything that we haven't been able to deal with
de todo lo que no hemos podido tratar
this week but my throat is itchy  it
esta semana pero la garganta me pica me
itches itches me a lot itches me a lot
pica me pica muchísimo me pica muchísimo
but well let's see a video
pero bueno vamos a ver videito
of sides in his project your first million
de lados en su proyecto tu primer millón
I have been in the Telegram groups I have
he estado en los grupos de Telegram he
gone to their mentorships and I have begun to
ido a sus mentorías y he empezado a
understand everything and I think that after
entenderlo todo y creo que después de
this video you will too I have no
este vídeo vosotros también no tengo
qualms about saying it already in the intro he
reparos en decirlo ya en la intro él
speaks clearly and so do I after what I
habla claro y yo también después de lo
have witnessed heard and read I am
que he presenciado oído y leído estoy
more than sure that what this man
más que segura de que lo que este hombre
has created is some kind of cult as
ha creado es una especie de secta a la
well as a textbook pyramid scam
par que una estafa piramidal de libro
But first of all a pyramid scam
Pero antes de nada una estafa piramidal
Who is am deo ya
Quién es am deo ya
dos m deya 2 is a 32 year old boy from Madrid
dos m deya 2 es un chico madrileño de 32
who comes from a wealthy family
años que viene de una familia acomodada
he studied at a private school and I also
estudió en un colegio privado y también
tell you eh For 32 years old he is que maete
te digo eh Para 32 años está qu maete
eh he looks like he looks like he is
eh aparenta que tiene aparenta que tiene
40 eh And he tried his luck at a very
los 40 eh Y probó suerte de muy
young age in racing motorcycles
jovencito en las motos de competición
then he enrolled in journalism at a
luego se matriculó en periodismo por la
private university and he left his studies
universidad privada y dejó los estudios
later to
más adelante para
go look at the side dude
ir mira el lado tío
to live in Australia there he begins to
a vivir Australia ahí empieza a
build the for a while without  to be
construir el un rato sin poder estar en
live a kiss balfer Thank you so much
directo un beso balfer Muchísimas
he's preaching the four
gracias esta predicando los cuatro
winds from dishwasher to Millionaire from
vientos de fregaplatos a Millonario de
50 in the bank to a million from
50 en el banco a un millón a partir de
there how how how
ahí cómo cómo
I don't take care of myself and I look younger
cómoo yo no me cuido y parezco más joven
than him at 35 Well quintuple I think
que él teniendo 35 Bueno quintuple creo
you've come a bit over the top also I
que te has venido un poco arriba también
tell you eh from dishwasher to Millionaire
te digo eh de fregaplatos a Millonario
from 50 in the bank to a million from
de 50 en el banco a un millón a partir
there he created an image on the networks
de ahí se creó una imagen en las redes
as a personal fitness trainer all
como entrenador personal fitness todo
kinds of videos help to avoid injuries
tipo de vídeos ayuda para no lesionar
that's the main thing okay I've been
eso es lo principal vale Yo llevo
training for 7 years and I have not been injured
entrenando 7 años y no me he lesionado
a single time he started doing mentoring
ninguna vez empezó a hacer mentoría
on how to create that content Here I
sobre cómo crear ese contenido Aquí
was better eh here I had a
estaba mejor eh aquí tenía un cuerpo
more natural body let's see I don't understand much about
más natural a ver no entiendo mucho de
fitness no but today's body
de fitness no pero el cuerpo de ahora se
looks more inflated and this one is like
ve como más inflado y este está como más
harder had on the internet and How to become a
duro tenido en internet y Cómo hacerse
million you see the
millon lo veis el
arm if you don't know this is Daisy 2. you will already
brazo si no conocéis esta es Daisy 2. ya
know her and her popularity has increased
conoceréis y su popularidad ha aumentado
so much that now she has legions of fans
tanto que ahora tiene legiones de fans
with a more direct and
con un lenguaje de más directo y
authoritarian language  he's telling the
autoritario le está diciendo a los
kids to wake up, to stop that
chavales que espabilen que dejen Ya esa
[ __ ] belly, you have a belly, you're lacking
fucking panza tienes una panza te falta
respect, you don't have money, you're
es a respeto tú no tienes dinero te
lacking respect, it's a [ __ ]
faltas al respeto es una fucking
shame that you walk around the world with your belly
vergüenza que andes tu panza por el
and your bank account empty and no, don't be
mundo y tu cuenta de banco vacía y no no
ashamed, he proposes very routines and don't be
te de vergüenza propone rutinas muy y no
ashamed of the empty account, you say
te de vergüenza la cuenta vacía dibes
as if the account was written on your
como si la cuenta la llevaras escrita en
forehead strict as if he were a sergeant
la frente estrictas como si un Sargento
and many welcome it as if it were
se tratase y muchos acogen como si fuera
a religion, I thank God
una religión Yo le doy gracias a Dios
every day brother for having
todos los días hermano por haberte
met you, loo the truth is I look at your
conocido loo la verdad te miro la
story, I get up at 4 in the morning, I go
historia me levanto a las 4 de la mañana
out, I take a walk around the block, I come
salgo doy una vuelta a la manzana vengo
eh And I start watching all your stories, I
eh Y me pongo a ver todas t historia me
have a coffee and I pee, 160 push-ups like we're
tomo un café y meo 160 flexiones como
doing now, yad has created a cult of
ahora venemos yad ha creado una secta de
positive thinking combined with an
pensamiento positivo combinado con una
idolatry of a superior being which is him and
idolatría a un ser superior que es él y
with an infallible method to make
con un método infalible para ganar
money that is
dinero que es
a controversy with sasel and now
una polémica con sasel y sigue ahora
sasel says that PlayStation Spain
sasel dice que PlayStation España le
paid him to defend the lodge,
pago a para defender al logio
no  I don't promise anything Kenny
no no prometo nada Kenny
welcome is that he's not going to give me the voice
bienvenida es que no me va a dar la voz
today I don't promise you anything but
de verdad hoy no os prometo nada pero
well if we get there we'll see
bueno si llegamos lo vemos
idolatry of a superior being which is him and
idolatría a un ser superior que es él y
with an infallible method to earn
con un método infalible para ganar
money which is a pyramid scam let's
dinero que es una estafa piramidal vamos
see those two parts let's see I want to know
a ver esas dos partes a ver Quiero saber
what the scam is What is the method of
cuál es la estafa Cuál es el método de
earning money the cult and the
de ganar dinero la de secta y la de
scam through his teachings of what I have
estafa a través de sus enseñanzas de lo
observed in the courses but
que ido observando en los cursos pero
also what his students transmit
también de lo que transmiten sus alumnos
and what thousands and thousands of kids
y de lo que miles y miles de chavales
right now there are 8000 in the
ahora mismo hay 8000 en el programa de
affiliate program paying 50 a month 8000 paying
afiliados pagando 50 al mes 8000 pagando
50 a month let's see mother of God Hey
50 al mes a ver madre de Dios Oye
wait what I'm going to have to give you some
esperar lo que os voy a tener que dar
advice I uh I mean
consejitos yo eh o sea
8000 is 400000 bucks a month
8000 son 400000 pavos al mes
400,000 bucks a
400.000 pavos al
month or so how is it possible that there are
mes o sea cómo es posible que
8000 people paying him 50 bucks to the
8000 personas pagándole 50 pavos al
jados and here there are no
jados y aquí no hay
balls to get there  to 3000 members that is
huevos de llegar a 3000 miembros que
worth 90
vale 90
cents and it's me a kiss Diego they are
céntimos y soy yo un beso Diego están
reproducing everywhere on the
reproduciendo por todos lados en las
networks By the way, before continuing, as she has been
redes Por cierto antes de seguir como
missing for a few weeks after
lleva unas semanas desaparecida después
the whole mess with the Mister Tartars and
de todo el lío de los Mister tartaras y
all this, I have not commented here that
todo esto no he comentado por aquí que
the third season
ya está disponible la tercera temporada
of the Club of Living Minds is now available, my podcast,
del club de las Mentes vivas mi podcast
we have interviewed a former
hemos entrevistado a una chica ex
Jehovah's Witness girl, her story is
Testigo de Jehová su historia es
incredible, the whole life in there
increíble toda la vida ahí dentro
we have also spoken with Memories of pz
también hemos hablado con Memorias de pz
with Borja from Endless Wars and
con Borja de Las Guerras sin fin y
many more chapters to come, I
muchos más capítulos que se vienen os lo
leave it here in the description on
dejo por aquí en la descripción en
podimo the progressive people always take it Eh They
podimo siempre cogen la gente progre Eh
will never take me, they didn't
A mí no me van a [__] nunca no te
pay you 400 bucks the other
pagaron 400 pavos el otro
day, but don't tell me your
día ya pero no me cuentes tu
life Why aren't there 8000 members here, I
vida Por qué no hay 8000 miembros aquí o
mean, why are there 8000 members of 50
sea por qué hay 8000 miembros de 50
where llado and here there are not 8000 members
donde llado y aquí no hay 8000 miembros
of 90
de 90
ctim what am I doing
ctim qué es lo que estoy haciendo
wrong, first commandment of this religion
mal primer mandamiento de esta religión
we are all winners but  give me all your
todos somos ganadores pero dame todo tu
money over there that pays for the lifetime membership that the
dinero por ahí que paga la vitalicia que
euro goes there you son of [ __ ] I'm going with
eur va para allá que hij [__] voy con
that from Colombia no then well the
esao de Colombia no entonces bueno la
room lifetime membership bro I'll tell you
sala membresía vitalicia bro te cuento
that currently I'm sleeping in the
que actualmente estoy durmiendo en el
car and I stopped paying the room to
carro y dejé de pagar la habitación por
pay the lifetime membership I don't give a [ __ ] anymore two
pagar la vitalicia me vale [__] ya dos
the riter for paying the
los riter por pagar la
lifetime membership But what does it refer to
vitalicia Pero qué se refiere a
lifetime to the to the fee of this I don't
vitalicia a la a la cuota de esto no
think
creo
not to the fee And why do you call it and
no a la cuota Y por qué lo llama y por
why do they call it
qué lo llaman
lifetime if lifetime here it is called what it
vitalicia si vitalicia aquí se le llama
is a payment for life that
lo que es una paga para toda la vida que
you keep
se te queda
continuously never show weakness
continuamente nunca muestres debilidad
never cry be a man whenever they
nunca llores sé un hombre siempre que te
ask you how is it And that you are winning and that is
pregunten qué tal Y que estás ganando y
how your students reproduce it tell
así lo reproducen sus alumnos disale
machine and brother winning winning winning winning
máquina e hermano ganando ganando
putting in putting in
ganando ganando metiendo metiendo
always the work eh What's up What's up how are we
siempre el trabajo eh Qué tal Qué tal
going around here winning winning we
cómo vamos por aquí ganando ganando lo
see it with a multitude of examples of the
vemos con multitud de ejemplos de los
kids that follow him this one says that he
chavales que le siguen este dice que
just got paid but now he doesn't even have anything to
acaba de cobrar pero ya no tiene ni para
eat because he had to pay for the
comer porque ha tenido que pagar el
course of sides I just realized you
curso de lados me acabo de dar cuenta tú
that I have zero that I was going to pay and it didn't
que tengo cero que iba a pagar y no me
reach me I said you how  I don't believe it I don't believe it
llegaba he dicho tú cómo que no me lo
but you're the one who made me
creo no me lo creo pero tú es que me
laugh you know the cashier was
hasta reído sabes la cajera se ha
left as you know this other one says that he
quedado como sabes este otro cuenta que
forgot his
se dejó los
tranquilizers But why are they telling this in
ansiolíticos Pero por qué lo cuentan en
public a kiss gaya I mean why are they
público un beso gaya o sea por qué lo
telling this in public if they're supposed to be making the
cuentan en público si se supone que
hard ones Why are
tienen que hacér los duros Por qué suben
these guys going up earning earning earning earning putting in putting in
estos ganando ganando ganando ganando
always putting in the work eh
metiendo metiendo siempre el trabajo eh
What's up What's up how we're going around here
Qué tal Qué tal cómo vamos por aquí
earning earning we see it with a multitude of
ganando ganando lo vemos con multitud de
examples of the kids who follow him
ejemplos de los chavales que le siguen
this one says he just got paid but he doesn't even
este dice que acaba de cobrar pero ya no
have anything to eat because he had to
tiene ni para comer porque ha tenido que
pay for the course of sides I just
pagar el curso de lados me acabo de dar
realized you that I have zero because I was going to
cuenta tú que tengo cero porque he iba a
pay and it didn't reach me I said you how come I don't believe it I don't believe it
pagar y no me llegaba he dicho tú cómo
but you're the one who made
que no me lo creo no me lo creo pero tú
me laugh you know the cashier was
es que me hasta reído sabes la cajera se
left as you know this other one says that he
ha quedado como sabes este otro cuenta
forgot his tranquilizers after
que se dejó los ansiolíticos después de
paying a fortune for his VIP mentorships
pagar un dineral por sus mentorías VIP
that the day I paid the 12,000 and some
que el día que pague los 12000 y pico
euros for the VIP the 6 months I threw a
euros para la VIP los 6 meses tiré un
step that the day I paid the 12,000  and
pas que el día que pague los 12000 y
some euros for the
pico euros para la
VIP 12,000 they pay for a
VIP 12000 pagan por un
VIP I'm going to die I'm going to die eh I mean
VIP voy a morir voy a morir eh o sea no
I wasn't feeling well I didn't know if that
me encontraba bien no sabía si ese
live And you guys aren't encouraging me
directo Y ustedes no me estáis animando
eh you don't pay me 12,000 for
eh ustedes no me pagáis 12000 por
any
ninguna
VIP Let's see you don't want a VIP with me that gives
VIP A ver no queréis una VIP conmigo que
you the
os pegue el virus de la
throat virus Phoenix welcome a
garganta Fénix bienvenido un
hug VIP 12,000 bucks And what the [ __ ] me
abrazo VIP 12000 pavos Y qué [__] yo
but how the [ __ ] I mean what I don't understand
pero cómo [__] o sea yo lo que no
is 12,000 You're crazy but I do
entiendo es 12000 Estás loco pero Yo lo
n't understand how so many
que no entiendo es cómo encuentra tanta
people will
gente que los
pay them 1,000 euros for a photo grandpa no no no
pague 1000 eur una foto abuelo no no no
but if we're here all day
pero si estamos aquí todo el días
begging for members and people have a
mendigando miembros y a la gente le
hard time paying for
cuesta mucho pagar los
members and we're here every day
miembros y estamos todos los días Aquí
gossiping no and it's a
haciendo salseos al chisme no y es un
coffee How the [ __ ] is there one that pays I mean
café Cómo [__] hay uno que se que paga o
why I mean I think they're
sea por qué O sea yo creo que son
people I think let's see trying
gente yo creo que a ver intentando
Find an explanation to This is okay I
Buscar explicación a Esto vale Yo
understand says to And how those people have
entiendo dice a Y cómo esa gente tiene
that money it's not like they have it let's see in the
ese dinero no es que lo tenga a a ver al
end 12,000  maybe there are a lot of people
final 12000 a lo mejor hay mucha gente
who don't have them in their bank account
que no los tiene en la cuenta bancaria
in their checking account as such but it
en la cuenta corriente como tal pero no
's not a
es un dinero
completely inaccessible amount of money let's see we're not
inaccesible del todo a ver no estamos
talking about 100,000 you know it's
hablando tampoco de 100.000 me entiendes
possible Maybe finance it or ask for a
se puede A lo mejor financiar o pedir un
loan and they'll give it to you if you have a
préstamo y te lo dan si tienes un
job 12,000 Maybe you can
trabajo 12.000 A lo mejor te lo puedes
spend it on a car no and finance it
gastar en un coche no y financiarlo
no So I imagine that they will be
no Entonces yo me imagino que serán
people who have so many so many complexes and
gente que tienen tanto tanto complejo y
maybe they don't have
a lo mejor no tienen en la vida no
many friends in life They don't get
tienen muchos amigos No ligan
much luck And so they think that they're going to This is
mucho Y entonces cree que van a que Esto
going to be the investment that's going to change
va a ser la inversión que va a cambiar
their
sus
lives I threw away a pill that I'd
vidas tiré un pas una pastilla que
had in my pocket for 20 years an
llevaba desde hace 20 años en el
anxiolytic because I couldn't I
bolsillo un ansiolítico porque no podía
couldn't I mean I got on a plane like
no podía o sea entr en un avión como
done now without the anxiolytic I couldn't
hecho ahora sin el ansiolítico no podía
impossible or The kid who became
imposible o El chaval que se hizo
famous for appearing on the
conocido por salir en el programa de
team program so you can see eh of course it's like let's
equipo para que veáis eh claro es que a
see an anxiolytic tell me if what I'm going
ver un ansiolítico decidme si lo que voy
to say is outrageous okay please don't
a decir es una barbaridad vale porfa no
let's say something that  let's
vaya a ser que digamos una cosa que
skate but I understand that the
patinemos pero entiendo que el
anxiolytic is to treat you a
ansiolítico es para tratarte
state not a state that in the end
un un estado no un estado que al final
is psychological mental no So in the
es psicológico mental no Entonces al
end A placebo yes you can
final Un placebo s te lo puedes
solve it many times not
solucionar muchas veces
some things no some things a placebo
no algunas cosas no algunas cosas un
let's say the placebo exists in
placebo vamos el placebo existe en
many things
muchas cosas
eh the placebo exists the placebo is a
eh el placebo existe el placebo es
solution in many things Eh many times
solución en muchas cosas Eh muchas veces
yes But it can have a placebo effect
sí Pero puede hacer un efecto placebo
well it depends If you are completely
bueno depende Si estás completamente
convinced if you are completely
convencido si estás completamente
convinced it is that in the end it is a
convencido es que al final es es un
state it is a state of fear of nerves
estado es un estado de miedo de nervios
of you know of worry So if
de sabes de preocupación Entonces si de
suddenly eh they convince you a lot a lot a
repente eh te llegan a convencer mucho
lot Well there I see it normal that it
mucho mucho Pues ahí lo veo normal que
has that
tenga ese
result let's see a placebo is not going to
resultado a ver un placebo no te va a
help you in some
servir en algo de salud
Physical health But I think that Mental Health
Física Pero creo que de Salud Mental sí
could solve sometimes sometimes don't
podría resolver a veces a veces no
tell me tell me what you think I understand that
decirme decirme qué pensáis entiendo que
because many
sí porque muchas
times the problem that we have are
veces el problema que tenemos son
worries fear anxieties about everything
preocupaciones miedo ansiedades por todo
not because of traumas or whatever they
no por traumas o por lo que sea que te
provoke you no but of course if you have a
provoquen no pero claro si tienes un
placebo that's the rules but of course it has to
placebo eso las reglas pero claro tiene
be a placebo that you don't
que ser un placebo que tú no lo
consider it placebo
consideres placebo
you understand the
me entendéis el
point Not in disorders and others but in
punto No en trastornos y demás pero en
something like anxiety overwhelm of course there it is for me
algo tipo ansiedad agobio claro ahí me
speaking of a thing of a fear of
está hablando de una cosa de un miedo de
getting on airplanes anxiety about getting on
subirse aviones de ansiedad por subirse
airplanes
aviones
of course the truth is that I have not had
claro la verdad es que no yo he tenido
many problems like that and I realize
muchos problemas así y yo me doy cuenta
if it is a placebo or
si es un placebo o
not that you realize that it is a placebo or
no que te das cuenta que es un placebo o
not Of course but I am talking to you about a
no Claro pero te estoy hablando de un
case in which you are in that you are not in that
caso en el que tú estés en que tú no en
you are convinced that it is not a
que tú estés convencido que no es un
placebo But well I imagine that it will
placebo Pero bueno Me imagino que
depend on research that he is a
dependerá de investigación que es
replenisher at Mercadona and that he has
reponedor en el mercadona y que ha
invested about 10,000 euros in a year in
invertido unos 10.000 eur en un año en
Yados and basically remains the same, let's say
yados y básicamente sigue igual vamos
millionaire, it is not euros in a year in the
millonario no es eur en un año en el
research team program that he
programa de equipo de investigación que
is a replenisher at Mercadona and that he has
es reponedor en el mercadona y que ha
invested about 10,000 in a year in Yados
invertido unos 10.000 en un año en yados
and basically if at 10,000 in a year eh
y básicamente si a 10,000 en un año eh
almost 1000 bucks a month
casi a 1000 pavos por mes
eh a person who works at
eh una persona que trabaja en el
Mercadona my goodness has spent almost his
mercadona madre mía se ha gastado casi
entire salary eh it remains the same let's say
todo el sueldo eh sigue igual vamos
millionaire, you attended a
millonario no es usted acudió en una
master class of j2 How has
clase magistral de j2 Cómo ha cambiado
your life changed  radically has removed my
su vida radicalmente me ha quitado el
stress worries something has taught me
estrés preocupaciones alg me ha enseñado
to live but in practice Javi How has
a vivir pero en la práctica Javi En qué
your life changed are you still
ha cambiado su vida usted sigue
working in the Super worries
trabajando en los Super preocupaciones
worries stress of course Worries stress
preocupaciones agobio claro
in practice Javi what has
agobio en la práctica Javi qu ha
changed your life are you still working
cambiado su vida usted sigue trabajando
in a supermarket No no it is a path
en un supermercado No no es un camino
ofdos if it were easy everyone would be a
deos si fuese fácil todo el mundo sería
millionaire How do you see yourself in a few
millonario Cómo se ve usted de aquí a
years Javier better than yesterday yte
unos años Javier mejor que ayer yte
Tomorrow how much money have you invested
Mañana cuánto dinero ha invertido usted
in it in the end it doesn't matter the money
en él al final no importa el dinero
approximately Javier it doesn't matter the
aproximadamente Javier no importa el
money you can change your life pay it
dinero te puedes cambiar la vida págalo
and that's it and as long as you follow his
y ya está y desde que sigas su
teachings How much do you charge per month I'm not
enseñanzas Cuánto cobra al mes no estoy
generating anything Look I tell you on
generando nada Mira te lo digo a la
camera I'm not generating anything but I don't care
cámara no estoy generando nada pero me
at all how I feel
absolutamente igual cómo me siento yo
And this is
más Y esto se
even more worrying because of the number of
aún más preocupante por la cantidad de
minors there are paying money
menores que hay pagándole dinero
monthly to them But this thing about
mensualmente allados Pero esto de los
minors that I don't understand
menores que no lo entiendo
you who have not left high school
yoos que no han salido del instituto
teaching How to be successful and financial freedom
enseñando Cómo tener éxito y Libertad
How success is not so difficult The
Cómo el éxito no es tan difícil El
Path to success can be one of the
Camino del éxito puede ser uno de los
easiest if you have the
más fáciles si contas con las
right tools in this video  I'm
herramientas correctas yo en este video
going to reveal and in
te las voy revelar y en
his private mentoring sessions the same a kid Running out
sus mentorías privadas igual un chaval
of class to
Saliendo corriendo de clase para
congratulate yados and tell him that his
felicitar a yados y decirle que le ha
life has changed I had to
cambiado la vida me tuve que salir de
literally leave class I flew the class Only I ca
clase literal me volé la clase Solo que
n't hear you Thanks bro right now
no te escucho Gracias brother ahorita
that I tell the teacher I literally flew away Do not
que le digo a la profesora literal me
worry Give it to him immediately
volé No te preocupes Dale caña seguida
Yes man pass through
Sí tío pasa
Thanks another telling him that since he
paso Gracias otro diciéndole que desde
pays for his courses at school they
que paga sus cursos en el colegio se
mess with him because he has changed his way
meten con él porque ha cambiado su forma
of speaking and this answers him sides I
de hablar y esto le responde lados tengo
just turned 16 and I have to go
16 años recién cumplidos y tengo que ir
to sios with institute then eh You
a a sios con instituto entonces eh Tú
what would you do in that case how would I
qué harías en ese caso cómo lo
face it if you could give me some
afrontaría si me pudieses dar algún
advice Well take me from a group of friends what
consejo Pues tame de grupo de amigos lo
you have to understand is that school is
que tienes que entender que el colegio
not real they are a whole bunch of
no es real son toda una panda de
useless people that is very in
inútiles que va muy en
line why are you going to educate yourself
consonancia para qué te vas a educar
what are you going to train with what
para qué te vas a formar con lo que
yados reiterates and his students reproduce that
yados reitera y sus alumnos reproducen
studying is useless
que es que estudiar no sirve para nada
bro Why are you going to study the [ __ ]
bro Para qué vas a estudiar la fucking
theory of relativity is that
teoría de la relatividad es que
paying to be taught some formulas you
pagar para que te enseñen unas fórmulas
understand so that you  teach theory that is
entiendes para que te enseñen teoría que
worthless in life this
no vale para nada en la vida esto nos
leads us to the next commandment what are
lleva al siguiente mandamiento para qué
the [ __ ] formulas for no What what are
sirven las [__] fórmulas no Para qué
the formulas going to be for No not at
para qué van a servir las fórmulas No
all it's like it's like like watching
para nada es como es como como ver
save me going to math class it's like
sálvame ir a clase de matemática es como
watching save me they are entertaining you with
ver sálvame te están entreteniendo con
little things and numbers
cositas y numeritos
damn dude but of course it's almost
[__] tío pero claro es que es casi
like normal that they esteem it no
como que normal que lo estimen no
also not of any religion that
también no de cualquier religión que se
seemed like it's us versus the rest
parecía que es nosotros versus el resto
we have the truth we
nosotros tenemos la verdad nosotros
are outside the system and the rest
estamos fuera del sistema y los demás
are the plebellos in the courses in all
son los plebellos en los cursos en todos
the Telegram groups all their
los grupos de Telegram todos sus
followers use the same language
seguidores utilizan el mismo lenguaje
Beyond the Meme of it's like [ __ ] I can't
Más allá del Meme de es como fuck no
last long
puedo durar mucho
Here I look to the right useless on the
Aquí miro a la derecha inútil en el
cell phone playing I look left another
celular jugando miro izquierda otro
useless one scanning on tiktok I look ahead
inútil escando en tiktok miro al frente
[ __ ] belly mirista damn dude what a
fucking panza mirista ostia tío vaya
bunch of idiots eh [ __ ] belly bro
panda de idiotas eh fucking panza bro
[ __ ] croissant bro of I don't know what
fucking cruasan bro de no sé qué que
everyone talks about Exactly the same
todos hablan Exactamente igual términos
deeper terms with more meanings
más profundos y con más significados
like despising the entire population
como despreciar a toda la población
because they are plebellos like  this
porque son plebellos como este
student What do I do with
alumno Qué hago con
them what do I
ellos qué
do counted
hago contados
eh You have to see you have to see The Plebs
eh Hay que ver hay que ver La Plebe
they are the
ellos son las
How plebs how is this
Cómo plebellos cómo está
student plebs
alumno plebellos
Sit down What do I do with
Siéntate Qué hago con
them what do I do they don't know
ellos qué hago no saben esperar sentados
how to wait sitting down eh I understand this video but for [Music] what to see you have to see they are the beasts the rest of us are failures plebs they have come out of the Matrix Listen an aside here to have taken your mind already two to another level the spelling mistakes how we handle them there is not a single damn accent in your entire
no hay ni una [__] tilde en todo tu
course There are a ton of
curso Hay un montón de faltas de
spelling mistakes and my eyes are bleeding
ortografía y a mí me sangran los ojillos
but what do I know I am a simple
pero que sabré yo que soy una simple
beauty of the system in a world full of
bella del sistema en un mundo lleno de
[ __ ] plebs where they don't even make
fucking plebellos donde no llegan ni a
ends meet and all they do is
final de mes y lo único que hacen es
swim in public pools with
bañarse en piscinas públicas con las
empty bank accounts full of
cuentas de banco vacías llenas de
[ __ ] Peace celebrating is like Oh
fucking Peace celebrando es como Oh
I am enjoying myself with my family on
estoy disfrutando con mi familia el
Sunday in the pool bro Poor your
domingo en la piscina bro Pobre de tus
children are not ashamed in the
hijos no te da vergüenza en los grupos
Telegram groups we see how
de Telegram vemos como continuamente se
this type of language is continually used it seems
utiliza este tipo de lenguaje parece
literally an exact copy of  all
literalmente una copia exacta de todos
the clichs that yados says and they are
los tópicos que dice yados y son
kids count on them very young
chavales contad con ellos muy jovencitos
some are underage 19 bitech
algunos menores de edad 19 bitech Muchas
Thank you very much for that member you will have a
gracias por ese miembro tendrás una
[ __ ] [ __ ] that will break eh
fucking [__] que que que romperá eh a
any elephant for becoming a member
cualquier elefante por hacerte miembro
Thank you vitc 20 years old have built
Gracias vitc de 20 años han construido
their identity based on being a
su identidad en base a ser un grupo
small and exclusive group The contempt goes so far
reducido y exclusivo El desprecio llega
that even such everyday things in
tal que hasta cosas tan cotidianas de la
society as going to a public pool or
sociedad como ir a una piscina pública o
public places to enjoy with your
a sitios públicos a disfrutar con tu
family for them it is an insult and I
familia para ellos es un insulto y me
get to the extreme that this case the
llegamos al extremo que este caso la
truth is that it moves me a little that he is a
verdad que me remueve un poco que es un
23 year old kid who has gone
chaval de 23 años que se ha ido al
abroad has left everything he lives in a
extranjero lo ha dejado todo vive en un
car the money you have he gives you
coche el dinero que tienes te lo da ya
two but he calls other people plebelles
dos pero llama a la otra gente plebellos
and [ __ ] for having a house I pass if you
y retrasados por tener casa paso si te
throw Ah okay so the rest of the
echas Ah vale o sea a el resto de la
people are [ __ ] for having a house and he
gente son retrasados por tener casa y él
lives in a car to be able to give all
vive en un coche para poder darle todo
his money to sides that literally charges
su dinero a lados que literalmente cobra
400,000 euros a month based on these people
400.000 eur al mes en base a esta gente
dude I have the wrong
tío me he equivocado de
audience I have the wrong audience dude
público me he equivocado de público tío
the [ __ ]
la fucking
gentlemen who are
señoreros quién sois
you I have the wrong audience dude
ustedes me he equivocado de público tío
from your house that in the end you're going to end up
de tu casa que al final vas a acabar
living in your car which by the way is
viviendo en tu coche que por cierto
n't yours either it still belongs to the
tampoco es tuyo que sigue siendo del
bank so it's going to
banco por lo que también te lo va a
take it away from you too so what are you going to end up
quitar entonces que vas a acabar
doing sleeping here on the [ __ ]
haciendo durmiendo aquí en la fucking
street and bragging that your sneakers
calle y se jacta de que sus zapatillas
cost more than a month's rent we're going
cuestan más que un mes de alquiler vamos
to break the dumbbells I've
a reventar las mancuernas ya me he
even put on my shoes the
puesto incluso los zapatos los zapatos
bosses' shoes Look This shoe is typical
de los jefes Mira Este zapato es típico
here on my Instagram that shoe is a
aquí en mi Instagram ese zapato es un
month's rent from your house bro no no
mes de alquiler de tu casa bro no no
but it's that he also pays for the verified
pero es que aparte paga el verificado
because I understand that this guy who
porque yo entiendo que este chico que
has verified on Instagram won't have to be it, he
tiene verifica en instagram no lo tendrá
gave Instagram like me
que ser le ha dado Instagram como a mí
but he
sino que lo
will have it MMM
tendrá MMM
dude What's wrong with m iden
tío Qué le pasa a m iden
today
hoy
Ah there it is okay okay
Ah ya
okay
está vale vale vale
this [ __ ] chat full of my
este fucking chat lleno de mistas
[ __ ] that you are not capable of let's see
cabrones que no sois capaces de a ver de
become members but no not the 90
haceros miembros pero no no del de 90
cent one is that there is I think there is a
céntimos es que hay creo que hay un
level to become members with 25 bucks
nivel para haceros miembros con 25 pavos
I mean how [ __ ] poor are you
O sea qué fucking pobre sois
dude you're a crazy person when it's
tío eres un pleo loco cuando es
literally a person without  home the
literalmente una persona sin hogar lo
irony of the matter is that this guy
irónico del asunto es que este chico
says that only those below you will raise you out
dice que solo te van a criar los que
of envy
están por debajo de ti por envidia
while he and all the students next to him
mientras él y todos los alumnos de llado
spend their lives criticizing the
se pasan la vida criticando a los
commoners for not having a Lamborghini or
plebellos Por no tener un Lamborghini o
dull lives who criticizes you dude If
vidas anodinas quién te critica tío Si
you receive hate you know who criticizes you
Tú recibes hate sabes quién te critica
those below you why
los que están por debajo tuyo por qué
Because you don't understand what you're
Porque no entiendes lo que estás
doing paradoxically the whole
haciendo paradójicamente todo el
speech is to get out of the system but it makes
discurso es salir del sistema pero tiene
sense it makes
sentido tiene
sense your life is not about what your
sentido tu vida no trata de lo que tu
body is doing [ __ ] up your throat
cuerpo está haciendo [__] la garganta
dude
tío
But let's see let's see I tell you half
Pero esto a ver a ver os lo digo medio
jokingly and half seriously on the part of
en broma y medio en serio por parte de
yado taking advantage of these people or rather
yado aprovecharse esta gente o sea
because you Maybe you don't know it no but of
porque tú Puede que no lo sepas no pero
course when you're on a video call
claro ya cuando estás en videollamada
with them and so on you see that they are a little no no it
con ellos y demás ves que son un poco
could not be considered on the part of
no no podría considerarse por parte de
sides
lados
you know how to take advantage of people
sabes aprovecharse de gente
they defend to the last
defienden hasta las últimas
consequences to comply with that same
consecuencias plegarse a ese mismo
system like the stock boy at
sistema como El chaval reponedor del
Mercadona all these people who go on
mercadona toda esta gente que hace
strike, who demonstrate because they do
huelgas que hace manifestaciones porque
n't want to work they are a gang of
no quieren trabajar son una banda de
ungrateful payments if I were your
pagos desagradecidos yo si fuese vuestro
boss  you say I don't want to work I'm
jefe me dicis No quiero trabajar estoy
on strike I say buddy Close the door
de huelga Digo e compi Cierra la puerta
from the outside please you're fired and
por fuera por favor estás despedido y el
yados himself tells you work work harder
propio yados te lo dice trabaja curra
than anyone Hey boss tomorrow I'm going to
más que nadie Oye jefe mañana voy a
get home at 8 why because I'm a
llegar a las 8 por qué porque soy una
beast and I want to help you What the [ __ ] is
bestia y quiero ayudarte What the fuck
going to stay like this guy Okay leave me
se va a quedar como este tío Okay déjame
a t that you have that's causing you a
una t que tengas que te esté causando un
little headache let me do it
poquito de cabeza déjame yo te la hago
bro you get home at 8 you do it You work
bro llegas a las 8 se la haces Trabajas
at 9 but for how long don't
a las 9 pero Por cuánto tiempo no me
[ __ ] ask me for how long you
fucking preguntes por cuánto tiempo
piece of [ __ ] useless Do it without
pedazo de fucking inútil Hazlo sin
expecting anything in return what are we doing we
esperar nada a cambio en qué quedamos
leave the S hostia well there I
salimos del S [__] pues ahí Estoy
totally
totalmente de
agree let's
acuerdo a
watch a second give me a second let me read
ver un segundo dame un segundo que lea
something wait a moment okay it's the
una cosa un momento vale que es el
title of
título del directo de
today's live [ __ ]
hoy [__]
listen to me the first one the first advice
escúchame el primero el primer consejo
that has given sides look that I would
que ha dado lados fíjate que yo sí se lo
give it to people Eh let's see without going
daría a la gente Eh a ver sin pasarse de
overboard either but to a certain extent to
la raya tampoco pero en cierta medida en
a certain
cierta
extent Exactly
medida Exacto
sisuka Yes sisuka to a certain extent Yes let's
sisuka Sí sisuka en cierta medida Sí a
see don't get me
ver no me
wrong we listen to two again
malinterpretes escuchamos a dos otra vez
that nobody Hey boss tomorrow I'm going to
más que nadie Oye jefe mañana voy a
get home at 8 because because I'm a
llegar a las 8 por qué porque soy una
beast and I want to help it's
bestia y quiero ayudar
going to end up like this guy, leave me a
se va a quedar como este tío déjame una
task that you have that's causing you a
tarea que tengas que te esté causando un
little headache, let me do it for you
poquito de cabeza déjame yo te la hago
bro you arrive at yes you do it You work at
br llegas a las se la haces Trabajas a
9 but for how long don't
las 9 pero Por cuánto tiempo no me
[ __ ] ask me for how long you
fucking preguntes por cuánto tiempo
piece of [ __ ] useless Do it without
pedazo de fucking inútil Hazlo sin
expecting anything in return what do we
esperar nada a cambio en qué
agree on How do I explain this to you dude how do I
quedamos Cómo os explico esto tío cómo
explain this to you let's see it's not about getting caught or about
os explico esto a ver no se trata de que
letting yourself be abused
te cojan de de que te dejes abusar
at work it's
laboralmente
not about that, I mean, none of
no se trata de eso o sea ninguno de
you and suddenly you're working
ustedes e de repente estáis trabajando
in a supermarket that you have a
en un supermercado que tengáis un sueldo
fixed salary that doesn't go by hours or anything and
fijo que no vaya por horas ni nada y de
suddenly something goes wrong well in a
repente se complica algo bueno en un
supermarket in a supermarket in a
supermercado en un supermercado en una
factory whatever it is and a problem comes up for the
fábrica sea lo que sea y le surge un
boss or a problem comes up in
problema al jefe o surge un problema en
the warehouse and you have to stay because you're not
el almacén y hay que quedarse que no lo
going to get paid obviously you have to
Vais a cobrar evidentemente hay que
stay or or or set That's good there are some that do
quedarse o o o set Que bueno hay algunos
n't there are some that arrive on time and
que no hay algunos que llega a su hora y
say this is my time I've done my duty and I leave
dice esto ya es mi hora he cumplido y me
or whatever  Imagine that okay here
piro o sea imaginaros eso vale aquí ya
what you're talking about is someone who
lo que te está diciendo es de uno que se
shows up early to work okay someone
presenta antes al trabajo vale alguien
who shows up an hour early to
que se presenta una hora antes al
work and gets to work or whatever well it
trabajo y se pone a hacer cosas o lo que
is a little different
sea bueno que sea es un poco diferente
But what would you be in a job where
Pero ustedes qué seríais en un trabajo
when it's time to leave
el que cuando llega la hora de salir
okay you're in a store and you have a
vale estás en una tienda y tienes una
line of customers okay or in a factory you
cola de cliente vale o en una fábrica
're loading a truck or cleaning or
estás cargando un camión o limpiando o
something has broken I don't know okay or there is or there has
algo se ha roto yo que sé vale o hay que
n't been time to get all the
o no ha dado tiempo de sacar toda la
production that was needed for an
producción que hacía falta para un
order that has to be delivered to a client
pedido que hay que entregar a un cliente
okay
vale
and you what are you one of those who stays half an
e tú qué eres de los que te quedas media
hour an hour more even though you're not going to get
hora una hora más Aunque No la vayas a
paid or are you one of those who says Oh 3:00
cobrar o eres de los que dice Ah 3 y00
is my hour I'm out what are you
es mi hora estoy fuera de cuál eres
is my hour I'm out because I'm
es mi hora estoy fuera porque soy
totally
totalmente
replaceable well
reemplazable pues
Giovanni If I were your boss at the
Giovanni Si yo fuera tu jefe en el
time that they had
momento que me que tuviera recortes de
budget cuts and I had one employee too many
presupuesto y que me sobras un empleado
because I couldn't pay five employees
porque no pudiera pagar cinco empleados
and I had to keep four you go
y me tengo que quedar con cuatro tú vas
out
fuera
Giovanni
Giovanni
Romero in a company when you are an
Romero en una empresa cuando tú eres un
employee of a company one thing that is
trabajador de una empresa una cosa que
not that you don't let yourself be abused and all the  r that
no que no te dejes abusar y todo el r
Okay and abusive treatment and things like
ese Vale y de tratos abusivos y cosas
that okay eh but you always have to
por el estilo vale eh pero siempre hay
row in favor of the company
que remar a favor de la empresa
okay in the end
vale al final
yes you many times you can say Oh but
sí tú muchas veces puedes decir Ay pero
this problem that has arisen this
este problema que ha surgido este
problem that has arisen is
problema que ha surgido es problema de
my boss's problem or the manager's problem if he hasn't been
mi jefe o problema del encargado si no
able to deliver the order then
ha podido entregar el pedido pues fuera
[ __ ] off no no no
tomar por culo no no no
no in the end it's not that it's not worth it It's not
no al final no es que no me renta No es
that I've already arrived at my time and they're not
que yo ya llegado a mi hora y a mí no me
going to pay me for this hour it's not
van a pagar esta hora a mí no me sale
profitable for me to throw an hour of free work here at
rentable echarle aquí una hora de gratis
this guy I have my schedule I have
a este tío Yo tengo mi horario yo tengo
my schedule
mi horario
You believe it We are a family
Tú te crees El somos una familia
Giovanni to a certain extent let's see I'm
Giovanni en cierta medida a ver te estoy
putting you in general maybe you
poniendo por lo general a lo mejor me
're telling me another case
estás hablando otro caso
but you also have to look out for the
pero también tienes que mirar porque la
company to do well because in the end the
empresa vaya bien porque al final que la
company to do well It's that you don't
empresa vaya bien Es que a ti no te
miss your
falte el sueldo de tu
monthly salary that maybe they won't raise it
mes que a lo mejor no te lo van a subir
but you don't
pero no te
miss it you have it if suddenly the company
falta lo tienes si de repente la empresa
has a problem with an order that arrives in
tiene problema con un pedido que llega
poor condition or a client that isn't served well If
mal o un cliente que no atienden bien Si
suddenly there's I don't know what Well maybe
de repente hay no sé qué Pues a lo mejor
if the company is so worth it you
si la empresa tan valea tú
too  you understand me or rather everything It's not that they
también me entiendes o sea todo No es el
pay you for every detail every
que te paguen cada detalle cada
move that you make whether it's for a
movimiento que tú hagas sea para un
promotion every move no no you have to
ascenso cada movimiento no
row also
no tienes que remar también
you hurt my back by working
tú me jodo la espalda por trabajar el
twice as hard and and I ruin my life to leave
doble y y me desgraci la vida para fuera
and
y entra
another Giovanni comes in that argument is from
otro Giovanni ese argumento es de gente
very conformist people very me that in that
muy conformista muy yo que en ese
sense truthfully we are
sentido de verdad evidentemente somos
almost always numbers in almost all
números casi siempre en casi todas las
companies okay but a person like the one who
empresas vale pero una persona como la
is writing to you here yado is not
que te está escribiendo aquí yado no es
a number I mean a person who
un número o sea una persona que se
behaves like that at work is not a
comporta así en un trabajo no es un
number haha work More than a man if you
número ja curra Más que hombre si tú te
behave like that you know what I'm
comportas como que como como el sabes lo
telling you like one Well
que te digo como uno
yes you are a number but a person who
Pues sí eres un número pero una persona
is like that is not a number Nobody Hey
que es así no es un número Nadie Oye
boss tomorrow I will arrive at 8 because
jefe mañana voy a llegar a las 8 por qué
because I am a beast and I want to help you
porque soy una bestia y quiero ayudarte
What the [ __ ] is going to stay like this
What the fuck se va a quedar como este
guy Okay leave me a task that you have that is you know I
tío Okay déjame una tarea que tengas que
have a company I
te esté se sea yo tengo una empresa yo
have a company let's is that in fact I have it is that
tengo una empresa vamos es que de hecho
in fact I have it and this is what I
la tengo es que de hecho la tengo y esto
'm thinking
estoy pensando se me están viniendo
many examples are coming to mind with my people
muchos ejemplos a la cabeza con mi gente
who work for me I have a  company and
que me trabaja yo tengo una empresa y a
suddenly I have a problem and there's
mí de repente Yo tengo un problema y hay
one who solves it for me
uno que me lo
you know what? Well, I always take that guy
soluciona sabes ch pues ese tío lo tengo
into account more than
siempre más en cuenta que
another who does what is fair. No, no,
no que otro que va a lo justo no no
these are my
estas son mis
conditions, we apply it here, I apply it
condiciones lo aplicamos aquí lo aplico
here, look, I apply it here. eh, the Editors
aquí mira lo aplico aquí eh los Editores
normally have a day off.
tienen normalmente un día de descanso
Well, a day off, I mean,
Bueno un día de descanso me refiero
they have as many days off as they
tienen los días de descansos que ellos
want. Because if someone
quieran Porque si uno una semana se
wants to go on a trip for a week, there's no
quiere ir de viaje Aquí no hay horario
fixed schedule, or anything fixed, or anything like that,
fijo ni nada fijo ni nada por el estilo
but generally everyone has
pero por lo general cada uno me me tiene
told me one or two days a week when they
dicho un día o dos de la semana en los
like to do nothing. Okay, so
que le gusta no hacer nada vale Pues
imagine one of those days comes around,
imagínate que llega uno de esos días
like Saturday, okay? And suddenly Auron
ponte sábado vale Y de repente auron
Play shits in Rubius's house. He
Play se caga en la casa de de
goes to Rubius's house, shits himself, and
Rubius va a casa de Rubius se caga y
Rubius hits him. Play And now
Rubius le pega una [__] Play Y ahora
I have to make a video. I say it in
yo tengo que hacer un vídeo lo digo en
the group. Hey, I know it's your day off,
el grupo Oye sé que es vuestro día libre
but this happened and everyone tells me it's your
pero es que ha pasado esto y me dicen
day
todos es el día de
off,
descanso
man. If suddenly someone says,
hombre si de repente hay uno que dice
Look, listen to me, pin
Mira escúchame pin
pan, and don't let me get lost, they'll solve it for me.
pan y que no me deje tirar me solucion
the problem man well I'm going to
el problema hombre pues yo lo voy a
have it in another in another in
tener en otro en otro en
another in another
otro en otra
consideration causing a little
consideración causando un poquito de
head let me I'll do it for you bro you arrive at yes you
cabeza déjame yo te la hago bro llegas a
work at 9 but for how
las se trabajas a las 9 pero Por cuánto
long no [ __ ] ask me in
tiempo no me fucking preguntes por
writing Pablo I was going to read it there it's
escrito Pablo por ahí lo iba a leer se
gone Where did
me ha ido Dónde ha escrito
Pablo write damn I saw that Pablo wrote
Pablo [__] he visto que ha escrito Pablo
and now I can't
y ahora no lo
see it I saw that Pablo wrote
veo he visto que ha escrito Pablo
while I was talking and now I
mientras que yo estaba hablando y ahora
can't find it here Here people have
no lo encuentro aquí Aquí la gente tiene
the idea that they get paid to spend a
la idea de que le pagan por pasar unas
certain number of hours in a company As
determinadas horas en una empresa Como
if that were of any use you get paid to
si eso sirviera para algo te pagan por
get a job done to generate
sacar un trabajo delante por generar
value if not it's no use but that already that already
valor si no no sirve pero eso ya eso ya
is a condition of the person
eso ya es una condición de la persona
Pablo you know that is already a condition of
Pablo sabes eso ya es una condición de
a person Above all you know what for me
una persona Sobre todo sabes qué para mí
for me you learn more maybe eh
para mí aprendes más a lo mejor eh
When you've been in jobs like me in the
Cuando has estado en trabajos tipo yo en
most humble jobs since I was very
trabajo de los más Humildes desde muy
young and for many years many years many
joven y muchos años muchos años muchos
years that's when you learn that concept
años ahí es cuando aprendes ese concepto
you know normally people who have a
sabes normalmente gente que tiene una
career work good
carrera trabajo buenos puestos de
jobs in decent conditions
trabajo en condiciones
Eh they don't have that
Eh no tienen ese
concept they don't have that concept they have
concepto no tienen ese concepto tienen
the concept that Ah I get paid  8
el concepto de que Ah a mí me pagan 8
hours I 8 hours and 5 minutes I'm not going to
horas yo 8 horas y 5 minutos no te voy a
fire you and it's how it is that it's not all about
echar y es cómo es que no se trata todo
that
de de esa
precision you know you when you start
exactitud sabes a ti tú cuando tú entras
a job what interests you is that
en un trabajo a ti lo que te interesa es
that job is eh first
que ese trabajo sea eh lo primero
stable and that's it Then the second is Well maybe
estable y ya Luego lo segundo es Pues a
ascending not in the sense
lo mejor ascendente no en el sentido de
that you go aspiring to more within the
que vayas aspirando a más dentro de la
company to get the maximum within
empresa a conseguir el máximo dentro de
the company and the highest possible salary that
la empresa y el mayor sueldo posible que
exists of that possibility within
que exista de esa de posibilidad dentro
that company okay
de esa empresa vale
but but of course
pero pero claro
in you have to see that in order for you
em tú tienes que ver que para que a ti
not to lack work you cannot
no te falte el trabajo no te puede
lack that
faltar esa
company so you in a certain way you
empresa entonces a ti en cierto modo te
have to worry about the functioning of
tiene que preocupar el funcionamiento de
a company I'm not talking to you about a
una empresa no os estoy hablando de un
Mercadona and I'm not talking to you about a
mercadona y no os estoy hablando de un
hypermarket
hiperc
you know Well maybe yes also no because
sabes Bueno tal vez sí también no porque
in a supermarket suddenly eh
en en un supermercado de repente eh se
you can have a huge queue
te puede juntar una cola tremenda
of customers and it's time to close
de de cliente y llega la hora de cerrar
And what do you do short Well if you have to
Y qué haces cortas Pues si te tienes que
stay 20 minutes attending to those sales
quedar 20 minutos atendiendo esas ventas
and the supermarket sells
y que se di el supermercado venda
more
más
damn it now but the thing is that I want a
[__] ya pero es que yo quiero un
percentage of those
porcentaje de esas
sales that's not the thought [ __ ]
ventas ese no es el pensamiento
dude how am I huh you piece of
[__] macho có estoy eh pedazo de
[ __ ] useless Do it without expecting anything in
fucking inútil Hazlo sin esperar nada a
return what are we left with? Do we leave the
cambio en qué quedamos salimos del
system or are we slaves to it? Third
sistema o somos esclavos de él tercer
commandment
mandamiento
isolate coercive organizations
aíslen las organizaciones coercitivas
saying that your environment is negative that it's
decir de que tu entorno es negativo que
not doing well and causing
no está haciendo bien y provocando que
you to isolate yourself from it we see it with the
te aisles de él lo vemos con los
kids who have gone abroad
chavales que se han ido al extranjero
leaving everything behind or this other student
dejándolo todo atrás o este otro alumno
from the sides who boasts that he doesn't talk
de lados que se jacta de que no habla
to his parents that simply he
con sus padres que simplemente él
knowing that he spends money with that he
sabiendo que él pasa dinero con eso él
is happy I talk very little with my parents I
está feliz hablo muy poco con mis padres
just make sure that he doesn't lack You're welcome
solo me encargo de que no le falte De
because my environment is very are
nada porque mi entorno es muy son
negative in itself you know then bro
negativos de por sí sabes entonces bro
I gave them the car they have money so that he does
yo les puse el coche tienen dinero para
n't lack You're welcome then with
que no le falte De nada entonces yo con
that Bro I feel good because I know that he doesn't
eso Bro me siento bien porque sé que no
lack anything I don't know how the saying went
le falta nada no sé cómo decía el dicho
But why say that about your parents on the
Pero ha qué F decir eso de tus padres en
internet how poor is the one who only has
internet qu pobre el que solo tiene
money I don't think But well all this
dinero no pienso yo Pero bueno todo esto
is based on the law of attraction in the
se basa en la ley de la atracción en la
law of the universe therefore you attract
ley del universo por lo tanto tú atraes
what  you surround and that's why This
de lo que te rodeas y por eso Este
message is so dangerous when they say no
mensaje es tan peligroso cuando dicen no
the law of attraction What problem is there?
la ley de la atracción Qué problema hay
Look for example this one of the
pues Mira por ejemplo este una de las
consequences is if your environment doesn't have a
consecuencias es si tu entorno no tiene
Lamborghini you're not going to have a
un Lamborghini tú no vas a tener un
Lamborghini your environment changes your family does
Lamborghini cambia tu entorno tu familia
n't understand you this is from the yad course itself
no te entiende esto es del propio curso
for me it depends a lot on what
de yad para mí depende mucho para qué
type of people you work for let's see what I
tipo de gente trabaje a ver lo que os
'm talking about It's not a general rule
estoy hablando No es una norma general
as such, I mean what I'm
como tal o sea con lo que os estoy
talking about doesn't mean that now I
hablando no quiere decir que ahora yo
get to a place that's paying you
llegue a un sitio que te está pagando
500 a month to work 12 hours
500 al mes por trabajar 12 horas
having you hired 4 hours a day
teniéndote contratado 4 horas al día
okay and and and what and that you let it until he
vale y y y que y que te dejes que hasta
tells you to clean the
que te mande que le limpies el coche al
boss's car or that's not it Look don't
jefe o sea eso no A ver no me seáis
exaggerate what I've told you I know it's a
exagerado lo que os he dicho se es un
bit of a general rule in
poco en Norma general en empresas
normal companies that are not abusive [ __ ] it's that you
normales que no son abusadores [__] es
also take everything
que también lo lleváis todo a lo
literally let's see if you're telling me
literal vamos a ver si me estás diciendo
that you're working in a garage and the
que estás trabajando en un taller y el
boss when he doesn't have work makes you
jefe cuando no tiene trabajo te hace
clean his car and he has you hired
limpiarle el coche y te tiene contratado
for 400  a month 4 hours paid and you
por 400 al mes 4 horas cotizada y
work 12 in reality that don't appear
trabajas 12 en realidad que no figuran
anywhere man there I'm not
en ninguna parte hombre ahí no te estoy
talking to you about that I'm talking to you about a
hablando de eso te estoy hablando de una
normal thing a very normal job where they
cosa normal un trabajo bien normal donde
pay you on your day they don't miss in the
te pagan en tu día no fallan en los
payments it's a company that works you know it's that you
pagos es una empresa que funciona sabes
also look for the excuse but
es que también lo buscáis la excusa pero
the thought Generally for me it's
el pensamiento Por lo general para mí es
like this one that has already said two you go to
como este que ha dicho ya dos te vas al
work a little earlier Well, in the
trabajo un poco antes Bueno yo en el
subject of a little earlier Maybe in my
tema de un poco antes A lo mejor en mi
case in the places where I have worked
caso en los sitios donde yo he trabajado
Yes but because ah well I'm not going to
Sí pero porque ah en fin no os voy a
explain my life but generally it
explicar mi vida pero por lo general
usually happens more at the time of leaving than at
suele pasar más a la hora de irse que a
the time of entering,
la hora de entrar
earlier they
antes
isolate your family from your environment to
aíslen de tu familia de tu entorno para
get that Lambo what are we left with another
conseguir ese Lambo en qué quedamos otro
student asked him for advice on a
alumno le pidió consejo sobre una
very delicate situation with his family and
situación muy delicada con su familia y
this is what he answered the case is that more with my
esto le contestó caso es que más con mi
ex-partner Eh, he won't let me speak on the
expareja Eh no me deja hablar por
phone with my daughter and he played that's the
teléfono con mi hija y el jugado aí la
reason but they don't penalize him with anything okay
razón pero no le penalizan con nada vale
Well you know what I told him, you know what he
Pues sabes lo quec le decía sabes qué
takes your [ __ ] [ __ ] children and eat
toma tus [__] fucking hijos y comer
[ __ ] [ __ ] in the logo of the
fucking [__] en el lgo del
country  lar I don't need you and they block you from
país lar no te necesito y bloquean a
all sides it's going to be [ __ ] weird with
todos los lados te va fucking rar con
GPS he's a beast of course at this
GPS ha una bestia claro llegados a este
point you think how is it
punto piensas cómo es
possible Wait I have to get the
posible Espérate que tengo que [__] el
context of
contexto de
this about a very delicate situation
estojo sobre una situación muy delicada
with his family and this he answered case
con su familia y esto le contestó caso
with his partner he doesn't let me talk
con es pareja no me deja hablar por
to my daughter on the phone and the player is going to agree
teléfono con mi hija y el jugado me va
with me but they don't penalize him
dar a mí la razón pero no le penalizan
with anything okay Well you know what I did he
con nada vale Pues sabes lo que hac
said you know what take your [ __ ] [ __ ]
decía sabes qué toma tus [__] fucking
children and v eat [ __ ] [ __ ] I'll get out
hijos y v comer fucking [__] me largo
your [ __ ] [ __ ] children country I'm [ __ ]
tus [__] fucking hijos país me fucking
gone I don't need you and they block you from all
largo no te necesito y bloquean a todos
sides it's going to be Fu of course he's
los lados te va Fu claro es que te está
giving you advice on a mature life
dando consejos sobre una vida amadura
this guy whatever advice as a father and
este tío sea qué consejo como padre y
as a father of a family or as a
como y como Padre de familia o como
person with a mature life apart from that
persona de una vida madura sea aparte un
probably a kid who is older than
seguramente un chaval que sea mayor que
him no I don't know if he will be older than him or not It's
él no no lo sé si será mayor que él o no
not clear what advice is this going to give you
No claro qué consejo te va a dar este
What experience do you have son eat [ __ ]
Qué experiencia tiene hij comer fucking
[ __ ] I'll get out of the country I'm [ __ ]
[__] me largo del país me fucking
gone I don't need you and they block you from all
largo no te necesito y bloquean a todos
sides it's going to be [ __ ] weird with GPS he's
los lados te va fucking rar con GPS ha
a beast of course at this point you
una bestia claro llegados a este punto
think how is it possible  that someone
piensas cómo es posible que alguien se
takes this person's words seriously
tome en serio las palabras de esta
and thinks that this is a
persona y piense que esto es una
worthy solution, I don't know about a
solución digna no sé de un abogado de
family lawyer, it's incredible, we know it. The
familia es increíble lo sabemos Cuanto
more isolated you are, the more everything will focus
más aislado estés más se centrará todo
on the figure, the more everything will focus on
en la figura más se centrará todo en
continuing to give him money and you will only be left with
seguir dándole dinero y solo te quedará
him and this brings us to the fourth
él y esto nos lleva al cuarto
commandment you shall worship the leader and the cult
mandamiento adorarás al líder y al culto
above all things. Excuse me
por encima de todas las cosas Disculpa
bro, why machine? You don't have to apologize,
bro por qué máquina no tienes que
man. This is brutal, you
disculparte tío esto es brutal me
totally changed my life in every
cambiaste la vida totalmente en todo
way, I had no purpose, I had nothing. Thank you very
sentido no tenía propósito no tenía nada
much. Seriously, I was even
Muchas gracias En serio es más tuve
thinking about getting a tattoo of the logo of your first
pensado tatuarme el logo de tu primer
million, all because you seriously changed my
millón todo porque en serio cambiaste mi
life. You even have your own prayers in the
vida tien hasta sus propios rezos en los
courses to avoid being poor and attract
cursos para evitar ser pobre y atraer el
money, it says there. Don't rest is for the
dinero ahí lo pone no descansar es de
poor. The calendar is for the poor.
pobres el calendario es de pobres las
Parties are for the poor. Telling stories of the poor.
fiestas son de pobres contares de pobres
Excuses and they speak to the system, to the
excusas y le hablan al sistema a los
commoners. We give light to hate, we give
plebellos damos luz al odio le damos
love, etc., etc. Other prayers to
amor etcétera etcétera otros rezos para
get rid of your belly. If you have a belly, you do
librarte de tu panza si tienes una panza
n't respect yourself. If you have a belly, you don't love yourself.
no te respetas si tienes una panza no te
If you have a belly, you are
amas si tienes una panza eres un
ungrateful to our creator.  God
desagradecido a nuestro creador Dios
God is present everywhere there
Dios está presente en todos los lados
is a lot of divine in everything he
hay mucho de divino en todo lo que él
says does and says that in the end he is
dice hace y cuenta que al final él es
only a Messenger of the divine my goodness
solo un Mensajero de lo divino madre mía
if you are The messenger that God has
si tú eres El mensajero que Dios ha
chosen I don't know what kind of God
elegido yo no sé qué clase de Dios
we have up there who are you but I'm
tenemos ahí arriba quién eres pero estoy
worried I almost prefer that it doesn't
preocupada casí que prefiero que no
exist I don't know what option right now
exista no sé qué opción ahora mismo me
fits me more we see that idolatry as
cuadra más vemos esa idolatría como
now we will also study it in the
ahora lo estudiaremos también en la
pyramid scam it is all based on his
estafa piramidal se basa todo en su
person in his supposedly
persona en sus enseñanzas supuestamente
divine teachings we are bringing together the best
divinas estamos juntando a las mejores
people in the world I don't know if you understand
personas del mundo no sé si lo entendéis
and there are more and more of us and we are
y cada vez somos más y cada vez estamos
changing more and more and more and that is a
cambiando más y más y más y Y eso es
brutal machine you are all part of it he
brutal máquina sois parte todos de ello
says that he is a superior being that doesn't
dice que él es un ser superior que ni
even talk to you about money sorry but
siquiera te habla de dinero perdón pero
yes literally it is called your first
si literalmente se llama tu primer
million your project But hey I'm not saying
millón tu proyecto Pero bueno no digo
anything I'm a simple commoner I haven't seen
nada soy una simple plebella no he visto
the light yet he is a leader and that is why
la luz todavía él es un líder y por eso
the haters go against him and he is the
los haters van contra él y él es en
one you can trust remember not in your
quien puedes confiar recuerda ni en tu
family or your friends he will
familia ni en tus amigos él te lo va a
give you everything without anything in return well that is
dar todo sin nada a cambio bueno que son
50  little euros a month or 100 or 10,000 to
50 eurillos al mes o 100 o 10.000 para
attend a one on one small change
asistir a un uno contra uno calderilla
with no change let's say you're only
sin nada cambio vamos solo le estás
paying him a Lamborghini a month and it
pagando un Lamborghini al mes y
really is like that both in the mentorships
realmente es así tanto en las mentorías
and the entire course everything is based on the
como todo el curso todo se basa en la
idolatry of his figure in assuming everything he
idolatría a su figura en asumir todo lo
says as truth and in reproducing it
que dice como verdad y en reproducirlo a
through your social networks I would not
través de tus redes sociales yo no
be here without you I don't know if you
estaría aquí sin vosotros no sé si lo
understand I mean this is us a team I mean
entendéis o sea esto somos un equipo o
my goodness what a
sea es que madre mía qué comedura de
brainwashing eh We are all part of this that is
coco eh Es parte todos de esto que es
so brutal I mean in I don't know if this
tan brutal o sea en no s si comedura de
brainwashing is going to be in history This is going to
chor va estar en la historia Esto va a
be in the books I don't know if you are
estar en los libros no sé si sois
aware yet and all that leads us to the
conscientes aún y todo eso nos lleva a
next thing to see pyramid scam before
siguiente a ver estafa piramidal antes
the mentors the now wrongly called
los mentores los ahora mal llamados
coaches were people with a long
coaches eran personas con una larga
career who had succeeded in something
trayectoria que habían triunfado en algo
and who shared their experience and their
y que contaban su experiencia y sus
learnings to other people from
aprendizajes a otras personas a partir
that extensive experience in a field
de esa dilatada experiencia en un campo
now coaches are being created like thieves
ahora se están creando como chorros
of all areas that everything is
coaches de todos los ámbitos que todo se
based on a big smoke bomb and  yaos is
basa en una gran bomba de humo y yaos es
the main precursor of this a
el principal precursor de esto una
pyramid in which he is above
pirámide en la que él está encima de
all superior to the others and in which he
todo superior a los demás y en la que él
teaches you to be his soldier to work
te enseña a ser su soldado a trabajar
for him with affiliate marketing, that's why you
para él con el marketing de afiliados
will find dozens and
por eso Vais a encontrar decenas y
dozens of accounts that
decenas de cuentas a punta pala que
reproduce llados' messages and that
reproducen los mensajes de llados y que
have their affiliate links because they are
tienen sus links de afiliados porque son
their students, they encourage you, they urged me to
sus alumnos te instan a mí me instaron a
be a recruiter of more people for these
ser captadora de más gente para estos
courses, for example, one through your
cursos si por ejemplo uno a través de tu
affiliate link Because you have a
link de afiliados Porque tienes una
page that reproduces content from sides you
página que Reproduce contenido de lados
pay suos 50 You take 30% and so
pagas suos 50 Tú te llevas el 30% y así
he promises you to earn up to 1,000 a month
él te promete ganar hasta 1,000 al mes
at first just by being another soldier,
de primeras con solo siendo un soldado
this reminds us of platforms
más esto nos recuerda Pues a plataformas
like Live that in the end those at the top who
como Live que al final los de arriba que
are the ones who earn money use you
son los que ganan dinero te utilizan
to continue recruiting soldiers and take
para seguir captando soldados y llevarse
commissions, so let's see so that it
comisiones entonces a ver para que me
is clear to me if So your great plan
quede claro si Entonces tu gran plan
to become a millionaire is to have
para hacerte millonario es tener a
armies of very young kids
ejércitos de chavales jovencísimos
republishing your content to earn
republicado tu contenido para ganar
four bucks because it's four bucks for
cuatro duros porque son cuatro duros por
each one who subscribes  and create more
cada uno que se suscriba y crear más
soldiers who in turn create more
soldados que a su vez hagan más
content etcetera you are creating a
contenido etcétera estás creando una
huge smoke bomb then some of his
gran bomba de humo luego algunos de sus
students already create their own courses
alumnos crean ya sus propios cursos
copies of llados In what vin no Let's see, let's see, let's
copias de llados En qué vin no A ver a
see, smoke bomb then
ver a ver a ver bomba de humo luego
some of
algunos de
look at it
míralo
goldman
goldman chico de
golden boy his students already create their own
oro sus alumnos crean ya sus propios
courses copies of llados teaching
cursos copias de llados enseñando a
others How to make money then it is a
otros Cómo ganar dinero entonces es una
nightmare that bites its tail because
pesadilla que se muerde la cola porque
in the end you are making money not with
al final tú estás ganando dinero no con
anything real but by telling others How to
nada real sino diciéndole a otros Cómo
make money therefore a beautiful
ganar dinero por lo tanto una preciosa
pyramid scam Why Because a large
estafa piramidal Por qué Porque una gran
number of kids who have invested
cantidad de chavales que han invertido
those 50 a month 100 more and more have not
esos 50 al mes 100 más y más no han
obtained any kind of real benefit
obtenido ningún tipo de beneficio real
because that is what happens as we have
porque eso es lo que ocurre como ya
seen in countless Cases above
hemos visto en incontables Casos arriba
and the consequences are sad kids
y las consecuencias son tristes chavales
living in cars leaving their studies
viviendo en coches dejando sus estudios
becoming copies of a supposed
convirtiéndose en copias de un supuesto
leader whom they will follow to the last
líder al que seguirán hasta las últimas
consequences not accepting any type
consecuencias no aceptando ningún tipo
of criticism and turning their backs on the rest
de crítica y dando la espalda al resto
of the world it seems very worrying to me
del mundo a mí me parece muy preocupante
Beyond the Meme beyond that it makes us
Más allá del Meme más allá que nos haga
all a little Funny some  ways
a todos un poco de Gracia algunas formas
of speaking and some phrases he says but
de hablar y algunas frases que dice pero
if we only stay on the surface
si solo nos quedamos en la superficie
I think we don't see the huge problem that thousands
creo que no vemos el problemón de miles
and thousands and thousands of people have. Damn
y miles y miles de personas [__] loco
right now I'm more curious to see this
ahora tengo más curiosidad de ver este
video man but it's an hour long and my
vídeo tío pero es que dura una hora y no
throat hurts tomorrow we're going to watch
tengo la garganta mañana vamos a ver el
Claudia's Nicolasa you tomorrow we're going to
de Claudia nicolasa tú mañana lo vamos a
watch it it's an hour long
ver es que dura una hora
man you know it lasts an hour notice that
tío sees que dura una hora fijaros que
I've been here for an hour more than anything we're
me una hora llevo yo aquí más que nada
going to see Pablo's thing Pablo's we're
vamos a ver lo de Pablo el de Pablo
going to watch it because I want to know on a
vamos a verlo porque quiero sabe a nivel
legal level but of course I think that
legal pero claro yo creo que eso
legally what reproach would there be I mean yes yes
legalmente qué reproche tendría O sea si
you want to pay him 2 50 bucks the
si tú le quieres pagar ya 2 50 pavos el
problem is with your father for having you
problema lo tiene tu padre de haberte
no I mean but he would be committing
tenido no O sea pero él estaría siendo
a criminal offense we'll see now okay
un ilícito penal lo vemos ahora vale
But as such I've been almost an hour
Pero como tal llevo casi una hora e para
reacting to a 17 minute video
reaccionar a un vídeo de 17 minutos
So no I'm not going to watch it today because
Entonces no no voy a verlo hoy porque es
I'm dying I'm dying my throat is really itchy I'll
que me muero me muero me pica mucho la
probably be there
garganta ya seguramente estaré es mejor
Claudia's better than La gata hombre it
el de Claudia que el de La gata hombre
lasts 50 minutes and it looks like it's going to
dura dura 50 minutos y se ve que va a
be
ser una
amazing but it's just that I don't  I'm not going to
pasada pero es que no me va dar no me va
give it to you and I prefer to be there tomorrow,
a dar la voz y prefiero estar mañana
well tomorrow, do it directly, do it
bien mañana haceros directo haceros
also directly, you
también directo entes
alceo. But well, let's see about Pablo,
alceo Pero bueno vamos a ver de Pablo
let's see if it's
vamos a ver si
legally valid, we've already seen the video
legalmente vale ya hemos visto el vídeo
of the cat. Tomorrow, let's see about Claudia
de la gata mañana vamos a ver de Claudia
Nicolasa, let's see if it's legally,
nicolasa vamos a ver si legalmente
eh. Because of course, I think it's not valid
eh Porque claro yo pienso que no vale
without seeing Pablo's video before seeing it
sin ver el vídeo de Pablo antes de verlo
myself and I think that
yo y pienso que
legally, at least with the
legalmente por lo menos con la
information that I have so far, which
información que tengo hasta el momento
is the video of the cat. I think
que es el vídeo de la gata Yo pienso que
not. Why? Well,
no Por qué Pues
because, because no, I mean, because I
porque pues porque no o sea porque yo te
can tell you that I'm going to give you very good
puedo decir que te voy a dar muy buenos
advice and that I'll charge you for it. Jos
consejo y que te cobro por ello José
Ricardo, a kiss. Another thing
Ricardo un beso otra cosa
would be because the pyramid scheme, eh, I
sería porque el sistema piramidal eh
think that in Spain it's not
creo que en España como que no está
allowed, but of course he doesn't live in
permitido pero claro él no vive en
Spain, if I'm not mistaken, he lives in Miami.
España si no me equivoco vive en Miami
Eh, then no, I wouldn't find where
Eh entonces no no encontraría yo donde
the criminal issue would be. Here, I would
estaría el tema penal aquí el reproche
n't find the criminal reproach because you can
penal no lo encontraría porque tú puedes
call it a scam in a colloquial way, which
llamarlo estafa de manera coloquial que
is a [ __ ] [ __ ] that doesn't make you a
es una [__] [__] que no te hace
millionaire, I don't know what. But well, he
millonario que no sé qué Pero bueno el
asks and you are  giving me do you understand me
pide y tú se lo estás dando me entiendes
or in what sense would it be a
o sea en qué sentido sería í una
scam I can't find it the truth is I can't
estafa no lo encuentro la verdad no lo
find it let's see what Pablo says
encuentro vamos a ver qué dice Pablo
he is Amadeo sides But okay but let's
él es Amadeo lados Pero bueno pero vamos
see let's see before before before the
a ver vamos a ver antes antes antes del
video before the video before the
vídeo antes del vídeo antes del
video You
vídeo Tú te
think that with this guy I can go and
crees que yo con este tío puedo ir a
report
denunciar a la
people eh So that I appear in the
gente eh Para que me aparezca en el
game with a chroma with the Cyber with the
jugado con un chroma con el Cyber con el
cyberpunk behind
cyberpunk detrás
you guys see it
ustedes lo veis
seriously Pablo one day we can publish a
serio Pablo un día podemos publicar un
video of a trial or what No because they
videito de un juicio o qué No porque no
keep reporting me no but one day one
paran de denunciarme no pero un día un
day we have one day I have to show you
día tenemos un día os tengo que enseñar
Pablo in action I mean Pablo in
a Pablo en acción o sea Pablo en el
court it's not like it's not like on YouTube
juzgado no es como no es como en YouTube
it's that there are a lot of people who say Ah you ca
es que hay mucha gente que dice Ah es
n't do this because you're a
que no puedes hacer esto porque eres
lawyer How many times have you heard
abogado Cuántas veces habéis escuchado
that Oh but it's that Pablo is that you can't
eso Ay pero es que Pablo es que no
say this because you're a lawyer
puedes decir esto porque eres un abogado
listen to me dude here I'm a youtuber
escúchame churra que aquí soy youtuber
yes Javi we want to see it I have videos I
sí Javi lo queremos ver tengo vídeos
have videos let's see I already had
tengo vídeos a ver yo ya con Pablo he
a trial with Pablo that we won
tenido un juicio que hemos ganado
eh And then pending there are a
eh Y luego pues pendiente hay unos
few that look like
cuantos que tienen toda la pinta de que
mother  mia rit worth a
madre mía rit vale un
kiss but of course in court
beso pero claro en el juzgado a mí me a
the truth is that he convinced me that's
mí la verdad es que me convenció eso es
what I can tell you the truth is
lo que os puedo decir a mí la verdad es
that in court he convinced me the truth
que en el juzgado me convenció la verdad
is that he gave a
es que pegó una
beating of sasc there that I don't
una somanta de sasc allí que no
see and we have we have now well I don't
vea y tenemos tenemos ahora bueno Yo no
know when because this is very slow
sé para cuándo porque esto es lentísimo
but at the moment we have a few
pero de momento tenemos unas cuantas de
lawsuits filed and more that we are going to file
demandas puestas y más que vamos a poner
because I am not going to pass to one anymore
porque es que no voy a pasar ya a una
I am in a plan I am already in a plan since I
estoy en un plan Ya estoy en un plan ya
pass to many people I pass to
que paso a mucha gente paso de
answer them in public
responderle en público
and the last few months it has been impossible
y los últimos meses es ha sido imposible
but well this modernity man
pero bueno esta modernidad tío no está
Pablo is not here he has already left or rather this
Pablo por aquí ya se ha ido o sea esta
modernity that there is a chroma here this what does
modernidad de que hay aquí un croma esto
the review give now that you have opened
qué da la review ahora que hayas abierto
your Instagram that you have opened Loli
tu Instagram que hayas abierto Loli ha
said that she opens the mailman but that it has
dicho que ella le abre el cartero pero
not arrived Oh neither I am no longer with
que no le ha llegado Ay ni yo ya paso de
that story I mean I am going to comment on the
esa historia o sea voy a comentar el
gossip obviously because I can
salseo evidentemente porque puedo
do it but regarding the issue of
hacerlo pero respecto al tema de que de
the lawsuit that we have filed against him if he
la demanda que le hemos puesto si la
wants to take it or not he wants to take it, let him
quiere [__] o no la quiere [__] que
do it  whatever she sees that she has to do
haga lo que ella vea que tenga que hacer
she already has the demand okay
ella tiene ya la demanda vale la tiene
she has it through various channels she also has the
por varias vías ella tiene también las
notifications she has all that is the
notificaciones ella tiene todo eso es lo
only thing I can tell you okay and if she
único que os puedo decir vale Y si se
wants to show up and she wants a person to
quiere presentar y se quiere persona que
appear and if she doesn't want to
se persone y si no lo quiere hacer que
do it then she shouldn't that is her problem Okay
no lo haga eso ya es su problema Vale
when he said all the things he said he
cuando dijo todas las cosas que dijo
seemed like a lot of chap ahead you
parecía much chap alante me
understand he is out there to
entiendes está por ahí para meterme un
strike me Pablo I made my bet
strike Pablo yo hecho mi apuesta
Okay my bet has been with the
Vale mi apuesta ha sido con la
information that I have eh with the one I
información que tengo eh con la que
have from the video of La gata I don't know if there is
tengo del vídeo de La gata no sé si
something else that I have missed
luego hay más algo que me haya perdido
okay but I would say no that there is no
vale pero yo diría que no que no hay
crime in what
delito en lo de
they left Okay now we will see your YouTube that you
jados Vale ahora lo vemos tu YouTube que
have opened even your Twitter without
hayas abierto incluso tu Twitter sin
running into him or with his legion of
encontrarte con él o con su legión de
followers teaching you how to live your
Seguidores enseñándote cómo vivir tu
life to have four Lamborghinis a
vida para tener cuatro Lamborghinis un
Bugatti and be successful with women
Bugatti y tener éxito con mujeres
polyoperated and with all kinds of luxuries
polioperada y con todo tipo de lujos
like yachts private planes etcetera
como yates aviones privados etcétera
etcetera You will also have seen a lot
etcétera También habréis visto un montón
of videos reacting to him analyzing it
de vídeos reaccionando a él analizándolo
from a psychological point of view
Desde un punto de vista psicológico
analyzing it from the point of view of
analizándolo desde el punto de vista del
marketing analyzing videos that
marketing analizando vídeos que
analyzed found reacting to
analizaban hallados reaccionando a
videos that reacted found in this
vídeos que reaccionaban hallados en este
case I'm going to do what I know how to do
caso yo voy a hacer lo que yo sé hacer
which is a legal analysis on whether what
que es un análisis jurídico sobre si lo
llados is doing could be
que está haciendo llados podría ser
criminal or not so you know
delictivo o no lo es así que ya sabes
look compare And if you find something better
busque compare Y si encuentra algo mejor
buy it but Pablo you have little
cómprelo pero Pablo te han salido
tits no Let's see you have them there that
tetitas no A ver te han salido ahí esa
shirt is tight there eh Pablo I
camisa te está apretada ahí ya eh Pablo
mean There I am seeing there I am
o sea Ahí estoy viendo yo ahí estoy
seeing me let's go this button is here
viendo yo que vamos este botón está aquí
tighter than the screw in a
más apretado que el tornillo en
submarine John welcome a kiss
submarino John bienvenido un beso
gorgeous I mean you're getting there
guapísimo o sea te estás poniendo ahí
tight tight eh you're getting tight tight
cacha cacha eh te estás poniendo cacha
Here we go when you undo this
cacha Aquí vamos cuando te sueltes este
button a contact lens pops out with my
botón se me salta una lentilla con el
nipple look compare And if you find something
pezón busque compare Y si encuentra algo
better
mejor
[Music]
[Música]
buy it some compare m madeo
cómprelo algunos comparan a m madeo
sides with a PONCI scheme others
lados con un esquema ponci otros lo
compare it to a cult but we're going to
comparan con una secta pero vamos a ir
analyze one by one each of these
analizando uno por uno cada uno de estos
factors I see it more like sexa than
factores yo lo veo más tipo sexa que
ponsy
ponsy
ponsy ponsy it doesn't fit me either it wouldn't
ponsy ponsy no me cuadra tampoco no me
fit me  ponsy sect Yeah but in the
cuadraría ponsy secta Sí pero en el
sense that of course let's see it's
sentido de que claro a ver es que
also the type of people who sign up,
también el tipo de gente que se apunta
man, you know what I'm telling you? And if
[__] tío sabes que qué te digo Y si
any of them could be
alguno de ellos podría ser
criminals, first of all, what
delictivo en primer lugar lo que hace
mados does is sell you a mentorship, sell you
mados es venderte una mentoría venderte
some supposed courses in which you're going to
unos supuestos cursos en los que te vas
reaffirm yourself as a person, you're going to, as they say,
a reafirmar como persona vas a como dice
vibrate at a higher frequency and you're
é vibrar en una frecuencia más alta y
going to be able to get out of the Matrix and all of
vas a poder salir de la Matrix y todo
this is basically based, as you can
ello se basa básicamente según puedes
see in their first courses, on making
ver en sus primeros cursos en hacer
bepi, getting up early, getting up at 5
bepis en madrugar en levantarte a las 5
in the morning, maintaining a
de la mañana en mantener una dieta
strict diet and a high level of exercise and
estricta y un nivel de ejercicio alto y
sleeping little. This. What does this do? Get
dormir poco esto Qué hace esto consigue
the 2000 a little bit crappy eh. Because you're still
el 2000 poco chungo eh Porque todavía me
telling me that getting up early is good because you
dices tú lo de madrugar está bien porque
can take advantage of that more
puedes aprovechar el día ese más
productive day depending on how you
productivo dependiendo cómo te
organize yourself. Not necessarily the thing about getting
organices No necesariamente lo de
up early is that it depends on what you're
madrugar es que depende a lo que te
going to dedicate yourself to, of course, the exercise thing is
vayas a dedicar claro lo del ejercicio
cool, okay. And the diet thing is cool, I mean,
Guay vale Y lo de la dieta Guay o sea
very, very cool, the diet and
muy muy Guay lo de la dieta y el
exercise thing is very cool, but sleeping little
ejercicio muy Guay pero el dormir poco
doesn't go hand in hand with sleeping little, you don't have to
no acompaña el dormir poco no tienes que
sleep what  you have to sleep you have to
dormir lo que tienes que dormir tienes
drink the water that you have to drink
que beber el agua que tienes que beber
fatigue and enter a state of
fatigar y que entres en un estado de
absolute
absoluto
exhaustion This causes you to
agotamiento Esto hace que durante un
be in a manic phase for a while in a
tiempo estés en una fase maníaca en una
very high energy phase in a very
fase muy alta de energía en una fase muy
high proactivity phase but that is
alta de proactividad pero que
obviously not sustainable over
evidentemente no es sostenible en el
time that after a month, after
tiempo que al cabo de un mes al cabo de
two months you are obviously going to break
dos meses evidentemente te vas a venir
down you only have to see the faces of
abajo solo hace falta ver las caras de
many of his followers they are
muchos de sus seguidores están
absolutely emaciated they have
absolutamente demacrados están
dark circles under their eyes And while they maintain
ojerosos Y si bien bien mantienen unos
low body fat levels
niveles de grasa corporal bajos la
most of them are obviously not
mayoría de ellos pues evidentemente no
at all but healthy now
están de todo menos saludable ahora bien
is this criminal well it would not be
es esto delictivo bueno no sería
criminal as long as there was no money
delictivo mientras no hubiera dinero de
involved not in that case if someone
por medio no en ese caso si alguien
decides to tell you that what you have to
decide decirte que tú lo que tienes que
do is sleep little eat little and do
hacer es dormir poco comer poco y hacer
a lot of push-ups and you believe it Well
muchas flexiones y tú te lo crees Bueno
so far so good but here comes another
hasta ahí bien pero aquí entra otro
factor which is money
factor que es el dinero
Amadeo j2 He basically charges you for
Amadeo j2 Te cobra básicamente por
holding group meetings with hundreds
mantener reuniones grupales con cientos
of people with him for watching his videos
de personas con él por ver sus vídeos
for having minimal contact with him in which he
por tener un mínimo contacto con él en
will enlighten you is this a
el que te va a iluminar es esto una
cult well it depends on how we see it
secta bueno depende de como lo veamos
but that is already a concept  more
pero eso ya es un concepto a más
psychological
psicológico que jurídico las sectas
than legal, sects usually have two fundamental crimes apart from other related ones that may be more sexual in nature etcetera etcetera But the two fundamental crimes that occur are one, a crime of coercion and two, a crime of fraud. Let's analyze
estafa vamos a analizar en principio
these two crimes in principle to see if they
estos dos delitos para ver si se
would be occurring in the case of
estarían produciendo en el caso de
llados. The first is coercion. The crime
llados el primero las coacciones delito
of coercion occurs when you
de coacciones se produce cuando tú
force a person to do something they don't
fuerzas a una persona a hacer lo que no
want to do and that the law does not
quiere hacer y que la la ley no le
oblige them to do or you prevent a person from doing
obliga o le impides a una persona hacer
something they want to do and that is not
algo que quiere hacer y que no está
prohibited by law. Well, when you force
prohibido por la ley Pues cuando obligas
someone to scrub the stairs for you at
a alguien a fregarte las escaleras a a
knifepoint or you force someone to do
punta de cuchillo o obligas a alguien a
whatever, well that would be a crime of
lo que sea bien eso sería un delito de
coercion. Now, for there to be a
coacciones ahora bien para que exista un
crime of coercion there has to be
delito de coacciones tiene que haber o
either violence, which in this case there isn't,
bien violencia que en este caso no la
or intimidation,
hay o intimidación
intimidation. How it usually occurs
la intimidación Cómo se suele producir
in sects, basically because they
en las sectas básicamente porque te
separate you from your entire environment because they make
apartan de todo tu entorno porque hacen
everything in you depend on that guru of the
que todo en ti dependa de ese gurú de la
sect and those companions of the sect
secta y de esos compañeros de la secta
that convince you.  that there is
que te hagan convencer de que no hay
nothing absolutely nothing outside of it and
nada absolutamente nada fuera de ella y
that in the end your only option is to
que al final tu única opción es
remain faithful to it, that would imply
permanecer eh fiel a ella eso supondría
coercion. Well, it could imply
una coacción Bueno pues podría suponer
coercion and in fact that is how it works in
una coacción y de hecho así funciona en
many of the sects. Here,
muchas de las sectas es aquí lo
the power of a
suficientemente fuerte el poder de
weak, weak, weak group of yados is strong enough
flojito flojito flojito grupo de yados
for that coercion to exist. Well,
como para que exista esa coacción bueno
as always,
como siempre eso lo tendría que decidir
a judge would have to decide. A law professor of mine said
un juez decía un profesor mío de derecho
that for clear cases there is the law and
que para los casos claros está la ley y
for doubtful cases there are trials.
para los casos dudosos están los juicios
In this case, it seems quite evident
en este caso parece bastante evidente
that they all speak the same
que todos ellos hablan el el mismo
language, that they all behave
lenguaje que todos ellos se comportan
exactly the same, that they all do
Exactamente igual que todos ellos hacen
in the end the same things and that there is a
al final las mismas cosas y que hay una
group pressure that is
presión de grupo bastante fuerte
strong enough so that
suficientemente fuerte como para que
someone feels coerced to the point of
alguien se encuentre coaccionado como
forcing themselves to continue
para obligarse a sí mismo a seguir
paying even when they are convinced that it is
pagando aún cuando está convencido de
useless. Honestly, I don't
que no sirve para nada sinceramente no
know, but a court could do something
lo sé pero un tribunal podría hacer algo
about it.
al respecto
I see it as weak there, the issue of
yo lo veo flojillo ahí el tema de la
coercion, okay, I mean, because there are 8,000
coacción vale o sea porque son 8000
people, if you leave, you are going to feel
personas si tú te sales te vas a sentir
coerced. Well, let's see, you can feel
coaccion bueno a ver tú te puedes sentir
however you want, but a  one thing is how you
como tú quieras pero una cosa es como tú
feel and another thing is what you
te sientas y otra cosa es lo que luego
know later eh the law let's see I can feel
sabes eh la ley a ver yo me puedo sentir
violated right now by your looks
violado ahora mismo por vuestras miradas
that well I feel it no But well no it
que que bueno me lo siento no Pero bueno
's not your intention no or yes
no no es vuestra intención no o sí tal
maybe yes it's also true but well let's
vez sí también es verdad pero bueno a
see I see a leak I see it weak or rather it
ver yo veo flito lo veo flojito o sea
would have to exist on the part of
tendría que exir por parte de
yados I mean no longer not even not
yados O sea ya no ni siquiera ya ni
even from the community you understand I
siquiera de la comunidad me entiendes o
mean it would have to exist on the part of
sea tendría que existir por parte de
yados some kind of pressure you know
yados una especie de presión sabes
eh I don't know I don't see it it's quite striking
eh No sé no lo veo es bastante llamativo
when you hear everyone with the bro
cuando Oyes a todo el mundo con el bro
with the [ __ ] with La Plebe with the
con el fuck con La Plebe con los
plebellos let's see man you're from
plebellos a ver tío que eres de
Cantabria you're from Betanzos not the United
cantabria que eres de betanzos que no
States in your life what are you doing
Estados Unidos en tu vida qu haces
saying bro show and doing all those
diciendo bro show y haciendo todas esa
series of crutches that jadodos does
serie de muletillas que que hace jados
in the videos Well it's a
en los vídeos Bueno pues es una
clear imitation that makes you belong to
imitación clara que te hace pertenecer a
the tribe that makes you consider yourself
la tribu que hace que tú te consideres
part of that tribe of sides of
parte de esa tribu de lados de
winners that have come out of the Matrix
triunfadores que han salido de la Matrix
etcetera etcetera you do it
etcétera etcétera lo haces
forced well that would have to be seen in
obligado bueno eso habría que verlo en
principle  No, and in principle,
principio no y en principio eso que
proving it would be the task of the prosecutor to
demostrarlo sería tarea del fiscal el
prove that
demostrar que existe esa
coercion exists, EAFA. Let's
coacción eafa a
see. Secondly, we would have the
ver en segundo lugar tendríamos el
crime of fraud. For a
delito de estafa para que se ejecute un
crime of fraud to be committed, there must be a
delito de estafa tiene que haber un
displacement of assets and deception.
desplazamiento patrimonial y engaño
What does this mean? You have to
bastante qué quiere esto decir Tienes
voluntarily give your money to
que darle tú voluntariamente tu dinero a
another person through deception. That is, if
otra persona por un engaño es decir si
someone tells you that in exchange for your money, I'm
alguien te dice a cambio de tu dinero yo
going to give you four gold bars and
te voy a dar cuatro lingotes de oro y lo
whatnot. Of course, but it has to be a
que te Claro pero tiene que ser un
deception, if I'm not mistaken, eh, let's see
engaño si no me equivoco eh a a ver lo
what Pablo says. Let's see, it has to be a
que dice Pablo A ver tiene que ser un
deception,
engaño
eh, in other words, a deception of the product that they
eh o sea un engaño del producto que te
are offering you in exchange. Okay, in the
están ofreciendo a cambio vale en el en
transaction, sanction, that is, for example, another
la trans sanción o sea por ejemplo otra
thing is that you consider that it is a
cosa es que tú consideres que es una
scam because Yado is giving you some
estafa porque yado te está dando unos
advice that does not make you have the best
consejos que no te hacen tener la mejor
life, nor do they make you rich, nor do they make you
vida ni te hacen hacerte rico ni te
the strongest in the world,
hacen ponerte el más fuerte del mundo
but that's already how stupid you are,
pero eso ya lo gilipolla que tú seas
okay, but the deception. He is
vale pero El engaño el Él te está
offering you the advice and you are
ofreciendo Los consejos y tú estás
paying for the advice and you pay him
pagando por los consejos y tú le pagas
money for dinner and he goes to
un dinero por una cena y él se va a
dinner with you and you  you pay money
cenar contigo y tú le pagas un dinero
for a video call and he makes the
por una videollamada y él te hace la
video call you, I mean, I see it
videollamada o sea yo lo de llado lo veo
more like an only fan than a
más parecido a un only fan que a una
scam, okay. The thing is, it's not sexual,
estafa vale Lo que pasa que no es sexual
but whether the advice works or
pero ahora que los consejos funcionen o
not, man, that's where you're the fool. Go see a
no hombre ahí el tonto eres tú vete a un
nutritionist. Go take some
nutricionista Vete a hacerte un los
FPO courses and open a business and
cursillos de fpo y abre un negocio y
go to a good personal trainer who will get
vete a un buen entrenador personal que
you going,
te ponga
you know, but he's not into you. It's
cacha me entiendes pero él no te está
another thing, for example, it's another
sea otra cosa es que por ejemplo otra
thing if I tell you, I tell all of
cosa es que yo te diga os diga a todos
you no, and there are 1000 people here and I
ustedes no y hay aquí 1000 personas y os
tell you, hey
diga Oye
guys, I have a
chavales tengo un
contact, I have a contact who brings me
contacto tengo un contacto que me trae
Apple phones cheaper if you
los teléfonos de Apple más baratos si lo
buy them through me instead of costing you
compráis a través mía en vez de costaros
1000, they'll cost you
1000 os van a costar
300, so I'm going to give you my PayPal, eh, and
300 entonces Os voy a dar mi PayPal eh Y
you guys deposit the 300 there and
ustedes ingresá ahí los 300 y os van
the phones start arriving and you don't get them. So that would
llegando los teléfonos y no os llegan
be a
los teléfonos Entonces eso sí sería una
scam, okay, because I used my means
estafa vale porque he utilizado mi medio
that I have my possibilities that I
que yo tengo mis posibilidades que yo
have for, eh, that's good for  use
tengo para eh que bueno para utilizar
your trust towards me too No, I
vuestra confianza hacia mí también No o
mean there would be a very clear dollo okay in
sea existiría un dollo clarísimo vale en
scam and and and I'm asking you for money
estafo y y y os estoy pidiendo dinero
that goes directly to
que va directamente a
me for something that I know is not going to
m por una cosa que yo sé que no va a
arrive you understand Here I on the side I would
llegar me entiendes Aquí yo en lo de
see Maybe something
llado vería A lo mejor algo
administrative if in your country
administrativo si en su país no está
the pyramid theme is not allowed like here in
permitido el tema piramidal como aquí en
Spain where I think it is prohibited okay
España que creo que está prohibido vale
But it is something punishable it is not something
Pero es algo sancionable no es algo
punishable for example Then the
penabad por ejemplo Entonces el tema
scam theme I see it as weak
estafa el tema estafa lo veo flojito
too Pablo Let's see what you say
también Pablo A ver qué dices tú
plastic that would be a scam if someone
plástico eso sería una estafa si alguien
tells you in exchange for your money I'm going to
te dice a cambio de tu dinero yo te voy
make you a millionaire for this Well that
a hacer millonario por esto Pues eso
would be a scam now in this he
sería una estafa ahora bien en esto lo
does it very well jados jados the first thing you
hace muy bien jados jados lo primero que
say to yourself No I am a millionaire and I have
te dices No yo soy millonario y yo lo he
achieved it like this But you do not chase the
conseguido así Pero tú no persigas el
money if you do things well
dinero si haces las cosas bien
irremediably you will end up having
irremediablemente vas a acabar teniendo
my money a Lamborghini a Bugatti a
mi dinero un Lamborghini un Bugatti un
mansion eh two girls polioperated
casoplón eh dos chicas polioperada
around etcetera etcetera but he tells you
alrededor etcétera etcétera pero te dice
but that is not the objective do not chase
pero ese no es el objetivo no persigas
money, that is to say, he's not selling you that you're going to
el dinero es decir él no te vende que
get money, he's selling you something
vas a conseguir dinero él te vende algo
as ethereal as personal self-improvement,
tan etéreo como la autosuperación
like overcoming, like
personal como la superación como el
vibrating higher, like leaving the
vibrar más alto como el salir de la
Matrix, in other words, he's selling you
Matrix es decir te está vendiendo aire
vacuum-packed air from the Sierra, that is to say,
de la Sierra envasado al vacío es decir
something that obviously can't be
algo que que evidentemente ni se puede
measured or discussed or anything like that.
medir ni se puede discutir ni nada por
And he also does it in a
el estilo Y además lo hace de una forma
very good way in the sense of no, no, and it's that
muy buena en el sentido de no no y es
if you don't achieve the objectives, it's not the
que si no consigues los objetivos no es
system's fault, it's your fault that you've done it
culpa del sistema es culpa tuya de que
wrong or that you haven't
lo has hecho mal o de que no lo has
done it enough or that you haven't
hecho lo suficiente o de que no has
worked
trabajado lo
enough, he's selling you totally gamer girl farts.
suficiente te vende pedos de chica Gamer
There it is and you want to
totalmente Ahí está y tú lo quieres
buy it, what can I tell you? We could say that
comprar qué te digo podríamos decir que
yes, he's selling something that doesn't exist and
sí que vende algo que no existe y que
therefore it's a scam. We could, but
por tanto es una estafa podríamos pero
here it operates, it's a scam in a
aquí opera la es una estafa de forma
colloquial way, it's a scam. Let's see, the
coloquial es que es una estafa a ver la
word scam is used many times,
palabra estafa se utiliza muchas veces
even among ourselves. Dude, you
incluso entre nosotros tío me has
scammed me, you bastard, you told me that you were going to
estafado cabrón me has dicho que me ibas
make me a good dinner and you made me a
a hacer una buena cena y me has hecho un
chop sandwich, you bastard, you scammed me, do you
bocadillo chope cabrón me has estafado
understand me? Now, something else is a
me entiendes ahora otra cosa es una
criminal scam, a real scam.  that you
estafa penal una estafa de verdad que te
are referring to the crime of charging
está refiriendo al delito a imputar un
someone with a crime okay I don't see it I don't
delito a alguien vale no lo veo no lo
see it eh I don't see it I don't see it and even less
veo eh No lo veo no lo veo y menos
pyramidal and even less pyramidal
piramidal y menos piramidal
jurisprudence And what does jurisprudence tell us?
jurisprudencia Y qué nos dice la
jurisprudence
jurisprudencia la jurisprudencia nos
tells us that for it to
dice que para que
exist it is more deception than scam I don't
exista es más engaño que estafa es que
even see The deception in it what I
ni siquiera veo El engaño en él lo que
see is that he is taking advantage of people
veo es que se está aprovechando de gente
who are not very smart I don't see it as a
que no es muy avispada yo no lo veo un
deception even he is telling you How is
engaño siquiera él te está diciendo Cómo
his life and how he considers himself the
es su vida y cómo él se considera el
[ __ ] boss You know I don't even know if he is a
[__] amo Sabes incluso no sé si es un
character or is he that
personaje o es así de
stupid It's that I think he is a
[__] Es que creo que es un
character a large part eh
personaje gran parte eh
he is there high laugh receives the money
él está ahí se alta reír recibe la pasta
and that's it and he has his money the scam The
y ya está y tiene su dinero la estafa El
deception has to be
engaño tiene que ser lo suficientemente
well enough articulated so that an
bien articulado como para que una
average person would believe it and for an
persona común se lo crea y para que una
average person to be able to fall for that
persona común pudiera caer en eso
having the minimum due diligence
teniendo la diligencia mínima
exactly exactly I mean imagine
exactamente exactamente O sea imagínate
that you offer Let's see it has to
que tú ofreces A ver es que tiene que
be something that anyone can fall for
ser algo en lo que pueda caer cualquiera
not short people you understand me  I wouldn't
no gente corta me entiendes Yo no le
pay Yad for Jado to wake me up
pagaría a yad para que Jado me despierte
at 5 in the morning you know what I mean,
a las 5 de la mañana me entiendes o sea
eh it has to be a
eh tiene que ser una a ver un engaño de
real scam a scam in which what the
verdad un engaño en el que en el que
[ __ ] in which people can fall
[__] que en el que pueda caer la gente
Imagine me opening And I tell you what example can I
Imagínate yo abro Y yo que te digo qué
give you what example can I give you man you
pongo qué ejemplo te pongo tío
know it could be a scam Look for
sabes que podría ser una estafa Mira por
example that Jados organizes an event in which you have to
ejemplo que jados organice un evento en
pay some tickets to
el que haya que pagar unas entradas para
go
ir a
see it is worth it as content as
verlo vale como contenido como
entertainment and and people spend
entretenimiento y y la gente se gasta
a fortune on the ticket and they already
una pasta en las entrada y ya se
show up there and he doesn't go and he had no
presenten allí y él no vaya y no tenía
intention of
intención de
going for
ir por
example a product is that it is becoming
ejemplo un producto es que viene siendo
better with something material
mejor con algo material
okay for example I think Pablo
vale por ejemplo creo que Pablo ha
gave an example not a moment ago that it
puesto un ejemplo no hace un momento que
was well I'm selling you something that I
era pues te estoy vendiendo algo que te
tell you is gold and it turns out it's
digo que es de oro y resulta que es de
plastic there you understand Well you
plástico ahí me entiendes Pues tú te lo
can eat it because you're not a potter you do
puedes comer porque tú no eres ollero tú
n't understand you see this gold and you say
no entiendes tú ves esto dorado y dices
gold p and then you realize with
oro p y luego te das cuenta con el
time or someone tells you that it is
tiempo o alguien te dice que es es
plastic there yes you understand they are
plástico ahí sí me entiendes están
scamming here Which  This is the topic that this
estafando aquí Cuál es el tema que este
gentleman is telling you. Hey, if you do
señor te está diciendo Oye que si haces
burp in the morning and you get up at 5
burp por la mañana y te levantas a las 5
in the morning and all these things, you're going to
de la mañ y todas estas cosas vas a
have a Lambo, a mansion, all these
tener un Lambo una mansión todas estas
things. Obviously, an ordinary person doesn't
cosas evidentemente una persona común no
believe it, and many times we have
se lo cree y muchas veces nos hemos
found that absolute scams
encontrado con que absolutas estafas no
have not been condemned as such
han sido condenadas como tales
precisely because of how incredible
precisamente por lo increíble que era
that scam was. For example, people who
esa estafa Como por ejemplo la gente que
sold a tram line many
vendía una línea de tranvía hace muchos
years ago in Spain, or a bus line, or
años en España o una línea de autobús o
people who have sold London Bridge
que gente que ha vendido y lo ha vendido
more than once, no,
más de una vez el puente de Londres no
people who have sold
gente que ha vendido
the Tower of London or the Tower of
el la torre de Londres o la torre de
Hercules, it's a scam from a colloquial point of
Hércules es una estafa desde un punto de
view, yes, we could take it
vista eh coloquial sí podríamos tomarlo
as a scam from a legal, legal point of view.
como una estafa desde un punto de vista
No, because it doesn't exist. The
jurídica jurídico No porque no existe El
deception is quite a lot. I mean, there is no
engaño bastante O sea no existe un
deception that would make ordinary mortals
engaño que al Común de los mortales le
fall for it. In the case of those who are sitting there,
hiciera picar en el caso de jados existe
this scam exists, well, it seems that no, it doesn't seem
esa estafa pues parece que no no parece
that it is quite a lot. Of course, what they are
que es bastante Claro que lo que te
selling you is smoke, what they are selling you is a
vende es humo lo que te vende es un
contact with them, a contact with another
contacto con él un contacto con otra
room, him being around certain
sala él estar alrededor de determinada
people who are not going to  take you
gente que no te va a llevar a ningún
anywhere no but well but that's what they're
sitio no pero bueno pero eso es lo que
selling you yados what I've said Eh
te vende yados lo que he dicho Eh
so there's enough deception for
entonces hay engaño bastante como para
you to give them your money I understand that no
que tú le des tu dinero entiendo que no
from that side I don't see it it could be that a
por ese lado no lo veo puede ser que un
judge determines that yes, in principle I don't
juez Determine que sí yo en principio no
see that there is a
veo que aquí ha
scam here, let's see the Pony thing that I don't
estafa a ver lo del Pony que tampoco lo
see either the Pontius scheme the
veo el esquema Poncio la estafa
pyramid scam is often talked about as
piramidal muchas veces se habla de que
a pyramid scam in which
puede ser una estafa piramidal en la que
some sell to others and others sell
unos le venden a otros y otros le venden
to others and so the one at the top
a otros y así el que está arriba de todo
of the pyramid makes a lot of
de la pirámide consigue muchos
benefits and the one at the bottom
beneficios y el que está abajo
simply pays well that's a
simplemente paga bueno eso una estafa
Ponzi scam a pyramid scam would be something
ponzi una estafa piramidal sería algo
like what maof or some
así como lo que hizo maof o algunos
others did in the United States but the thing is that this one
otros en Estados Unidos pero es que este
would have to guarantee you a
tendría que garantizarte unas
return on your money and those
rentabilidades a tu dinero y esas
returns are only given by the payment
rentabilidades solo se dan por el pago
that the new partners who are
que van haciendo los nuevos socios que
entering that scam make in this case it
van entrando en esa estafa en este caso
is not like that basically because he does not
no es así básicamente porque él no te
offer you any return on your
ofrece ninguna rentabilidad por tu
money he simply offers you a
dinero él Simplemente te ofrece una
commission a referral a commission for
comisión un referido una comisión por
all the people that you bring to his channel to his
toda la gente que tú traigas a su canal
story to his mentorship to his life yes
a su historia a su mentoría a su vida si
you bring someone who is going to pay those
tú traes a a alguien que va a pagar esos
50 euros a month those 1000 euros a month those
50 eur al mes esos 1000 eur al mes esas
bip rooms those 30,000 that whatever it is, they are
salas bips esos 30.000 eso lo que sea a
going to give you 30% and they are going to keep
ti te va a dar un 30% y se va a quedar
70% for no So it is a
con el 70 por no Entonces es un esquema
ponci scheme not exactly because they are not
ponci no exactamente porque no te está
offering you any profitability they are
ofreciendo ninguna rentabilidad te está
commissioning you for what they do On the other
comisionando por lo que hace Por otra
hand we have the territorial issue he
parte tenemos el tema territorial él
does all this from Miami or most
hace todo esto desde Miami o la mayoría
of his time he does it from Miami we
de su tiempo lo hace desde Miami
would have to abide by what the
tendríamos que estar a lo que digan las
American laws say why Because yes it is possible that
leyes americanas por qué Porque si puede
a crime is committed by a
ser que se produzca un delito de un
Spaniard abroad and that
español en el extranjero Y que sea
the Spanish courts are competent to
competente los tribunales españoles para
judge him but for that the crime
juzgarlo pero para ello el delito
committed has to be a crime both in
cometido tiene que ser delito tanto en
the country where it occurred in the United
el país donde se ha producido en Estados
States as in Spain and here we have
Unidos como en España y aquí no tenemos
nothing Of course it is like that we have nothing Of
nada Claro que sea así no tenemos nada
course in the United States what they do on
Claro que en Estados Unidos lo que hace
both sides is a crime In short
lados sea delito En definitiva
what I have told you eh I have been right eh
lo que os he dicho eh he acertado eh
Pablo I am going to go with you to practice now
Pablo me voy a ir contigo de práctica ya
eh listen to me Nan there is nothing illegal or
eh escúchame Nan no hay nada ilegal o
criticizable in everything  you want
sea criticable todo lo que tú quieras
okay but
vale pero
illegal short short we do
ilegal cortito
n't know Eh there have been no
cortito no lo sabemos Eh no ha habido
complaints yet that we know of
denuncias todavía que sepamos con
regarding those found that lead us to
respecto a hallados que nos lleven a
think that there may be some kind of
pensar que que puede haber algún tipo de
scam or some kind of
estafa o algún tipo de
coercion I don't rule out that it may be
coacción no descarto que que así lo sea
but for now we can't
pero por lo pronto no lo
guarantee it nothing more to
podemos garantizar nada más daros las
thank those who support me very well very
gracias a los que me apoyáis muy bien
well very well very good video eh Very
muy bien muy bien muy buen vídeo eh Muy
good video eh Very good video well I'm
buen vídeo eh Muy buen vídeo pues Me he
speechless But let's see, many
quedado cuadron Pero a ver es que muchas
times you have the concept that you don't like
veces ustedes tenéis el concepto de que
someone okay And then by
alguien os cae mal vale Y entonces por
balls it is reportable what they do let's
[__] es denunciable lo que hace vamos
see no [ __ ] one thing is criticizable
a ver no [__] una cosa es criticable
another thing is telling people that they see
otra cosa es decirle a la gente que ve
that it is strong not what is happening and
que es fuerte no lo que está pasando y
the people who But well but it's
la de gente que Pero bueno pero es que
another or already that it is illegal punishable you
otra oa ya es que sea ilegal punible me
understand very good video this Pablo very
entiendes muy buen vídeo este Pablo muy
good video The truth is I liked it I liked it you you you I
buen vídeo La verdad me ha molado me ha
told you I told you this
molado te lo te lo te lo dije yo este
video I told you that you should do it was
vídeo te lo dije yo que lo hicieras fue
my idea I deserve my commission my 30%
idea mía merezco mi comisión mi 30%
pyramid if it were illegal it was already  in
piramidal si fuera ilegal ya estaba en
jail Let's see you have to be very
la cárcel A ver tienes que ser muy
shameless let's see there is one eh I mean
Sinvergüenza a ver que lo hay eh o sea
we've seen them but you have to be very
los hemos visto pero tienes que ser muy
very shameless very short for you to
muy Sinvergüenza muy corto para tú
commit such a such such such
ponerte a cometer un acto tan tan tan
big act of so much money and that it's
tan grande de tantísimo dinero y que sea
criminal and that you haven't even
delictivo y que ni siquiera te hayas
advised yourself so publicly or do you
asesorado tan públicamente oa es que Tú
realize that he eh he knows that he's
date cuenta que él eh él sabe que está
bringing in a lot of money you know that he's
ingresando un dineral ya lo sabes que
bringing in a lot of money
está ingresando un montón de dineral
surely laughing at those who pay it it's that
riéndose seguramente de los que lo pagan
To laugh Okay so you
es que es Para reírse Vale entonces tú
think that he has never consulted and
te crees que él nunca se ha asesorado y
has reviewed everything he
le ha pegado un repaso a todo lo que
does under some good lawyer or whatever
hace bajo bajo algún buen abogado o lo
tells him Hey this way yes, this way no I mean you have to be
que sea que le diga Oye por aquí sí por
you have to
aquí no O sea tienes que ser tienes que
be a kamikaze
ser un kamikase
you know you have to be a camicas you
sabes tienes que ser un camicas tú te
can make mistakes in things in life
puedes equivocar en cosas en la vida
but another thing is that you are
pero otra cosa es que seas
stupid okay very good video
tonto vale muy buen vídeo
this subscribe to Pablo's Channel
este suscribiros al Canal del Pablo
guys I'm going I'm going to take care of my
chicos me voy me voy a cuidar mi
throat okay I'm going to take care of my throat I do
garganta vale me voy a cuidar mi
n't know if I will appear tomorrow or not
garganta no sé si apareceré mañana o no
during the day  because I want to be
durante el día porque quiero estar ya
well at night
bien por la noche
to be able to play some telesalseo tomorrow
para para darle caña a telesalseo mañana
okay a kiss gorgeous I love you very much
vale un beso guapísimos os quiero mucho
Rest well
Que descanséis